(Mashle: Magic and Muscle)
To be honest, I'm quite surprised.
Abyss.
Other than Rayne,
there are other students
who can fight against his Evil Eye.
It's hard to imagine
someone better at magic
than the Divine Visionary, Rayne.
Could it be that you...
Ah, um.
What's wrong with you?
No, nothing.
Please continue.
You seem to be a rare talent
with great potential.
Hm.
But someone as outstanding as you
should be able to clearly recognize
that there is no real
equality in this world.
I've said it before,
our nature is that of beasts.
I can't tolerate the
existence of inferior genes.
Those who enjoy unearned success
become arrogant
once they are treated kindly.
They just go around
advocating their rights.
Don't you find them shameless?
We don't need to carry such burdens.
So, you meant
people who can't use magic...
Yes, that's right.
They should all be executed.
Shocking.
They are just being isolated for now,
that is not enough.
I want to change the situation.
Of course, it also includes other burdens
and those who protect them.
Those who protect them?
Mashle.
You're such a gentle and honest child.
You can do a double backflip
at such a young age!
Here, have my cream puff too...
You ate it before I finished talking.
Mashle, I'm so proud of you.
Is that so? Well.
In that case, I'm in a dilemma.
It seems we can't get along well.
Is that so? It seems you
don't understand what I said.
You don't seem very bright.
We can't leave inferior genes untreated.
I did so much work today.
Eh? Why's the door broken?
Lord Abel is fighting that mushroom head.
Now of all times.
Acid was injected into those puppets.
You better be careful.
Is that so?
How does he plan to deal with this?
With just one throw,
he knocked them all down without
even touching the acid puppets.
Hey.
You just said something
about inferior genes, right?
If I win,
does that mean you have the inferior gene?
You're quite stubborn.
Also,
where is Lemon?
Lemon? I don't know
who you're talking about.
I just absorbed some magic
power from those people.
Just?
Everyone is getting weaker because of you.
I've said it.
The exploitation of the weak by the strong
is their natural right.
You can't even stop their magic
power from being absorbed.
And that's exactly your current level.
It's over!
This guy
is stronger than when I last saw him.
You said the exploitation
of the weak by the strong
is their natural right, right?
So,
if I win, you'll tell me
where Lemon is.
I might as well go back home.
It seems you do have
the strength to talk big.
Thank you.
But there's nothing more than that.
What was that just now?
Sorry.
It's a bit monotonous going on like this.
There's no fun.
Finn...
He's your friend, right?
I brought him here to have some fun.
Your spiky-head friend has
been severely injured
and can no longer be of any use.
I hope you can show me something exciting.
Did I say you could take action?
Sorry, you're not allowed to do so.
If you don't follow the rules,
he'll be torn to pieces.
Is that so?
You can really do such a thing?
Well, unless you don't care about
your friend being torn apart.
Otherwise,
you'll be the one torn apart first.
Can't you do it?
Can't you give up your friend?
After all, everyone wants
to be a good person.
But like I said,
it's a lie.
The weapon broke first.
It seems you still think
you're an unfathomable person.
There is a war!
Ah, right.
You said earlier you wanted to
earn gold credit coins, right?
Are you finally going to give them to me?
Well, if you really want them...
He used a credit coin to
break the silk threads...
Sorry.
This credit coin seems to
be very attached to me.
I'm tired of your constant provocations.
Sorry, I don't want to
play with you anymore.
It's useless.
This isn't a power humans
can fight against.
In the end,
you're just a manipulated human.
I don't care about what you said.
For what you've done
to my friends,
I'll definitely make you regret it.
Marioness Change.
It's really admirable.
I didn't expect you to
make me use this magic.
But the fact of the survival
of the fittest hasn't changed.
It's only natural for
the weak to be devoured.
In my eyes,
you're just a clever rabbit.
I'll take the credit coins.
You've worked hard as a rabbit,
but a rabbit is just a rabbit.
It can't become a wolf.
What's this?
Why is the cream puff
I hid in my chest here?
Usually, people don't put cream
puffs directly in their chest.
Why?
He's completely turned into a puppet.
How can he still move on his own?
The principle of puppetization is to cut
off the electrical signals from the brain,
so as to take control of the body.
He should be immobile.
Could it be
a spinal reflex?
Spinal reflex.
When people touch something
hot, their hand retracts.
A light tap on the lower part of the
kneecap causes a knee-jerk reflex.
Reflex arcs like these,
which quickly respond to
external threats without
involving the brain,
also exist inside the human body.
My magic
turns a person's shell
into a puppet to control them.
But inside, it's still a human body.
If they can still move autonomously
after becoming a puppet,
I can't think of any other situation
besides spinal reflexes.
In other words,
it's an unconscious defense reaction.
Why is he so reluctant?
It's just a cream puff!
Does he hate it so much
that his cream puff was stolen?
If this is a world of
the survival of the fittest,
then it's only natural to resist
when being plundered.
Fine, I acknowledge your actions.
I can extract magic power from puppets
and use it for myself.
I'll use the strongest spell
to defeat you.
Marioness Secondth.
Harm Puppet.
This spell
can turn everyone within
a 100-meter radius into puppets.
The moment the silk thread touches
the body, the puppetization starts.
Of course, you can't possibly
see those silk threads.
In that case, I also…
The moment the falling silk
thread touches you,
your body will lose control
and you won't be able to break free.
I will play with your
puppetized body at will,
until it can no longer recover.
This is my respect for you.
The lion fights the rabbit
with all its might.
I've done enough for you.
Consider this my gift in return.
Huh, am I being thanked?
How did you dodge puppetization?
I cut all the silk threads.
Impossible.
No way you can see
those hanging silk threads.
It's not something humans
can fight against.
I saw them.
This guy unbelievably tilted his body
after Lord Abel used magic.
Now that I think about it,
he deliberately tilted his body
to delay contact with the silk thread.
The moment his left side
touched the silk thread
and his right side hadn't lost control
yet, he tore all the silk threads!
What a wild and sharp strategy.
It's impossible.
This is simply inhuman.
What is it?
You're sweating, Mr. Rabbit.
This is so interesting.
Mashle Burnedead!
I never had such thoughts.
Erector spinae magic.
Hell Fall.
I…
I am the rabbit.
My mother was a very gentle,
compassionate person.
Although she was a noble,
she always treated low-ranking people
equally.
My mother once said,
we just happened to be born
in a privileged environment.
But one day, my gentle
mother was assassinated.
That day, as usual,
she was distributing food to the poor.
But a man wanted to take all the food.
My mother was killed
in the confrontation with him.
That man said,
you're too naive and kind,
and you deserve to be stabbed.
I used to believe that
people are born good.
As a noble lady,
an innocent lady,
my gentle mother left me.
My mother was actually wrong.
There's no need for us to
have sympathy for them.
People at the bottom
have their reasons for being there.
We can never coexist peacefully.
For my own purpose,
I started gathering talented people.
Starting with Abyss, I looked for those who were
extremely dissatisfied with the current situation.
And I touched a power that
should never be touched.
All of this is for my purpose.
My thoughts have never changed.
It's natural for the weak
at the bottom to be hunted.
It's more like they must be hunted.
Bad people are bad,
no matter what are their origins.
Most of the stupid ones are at the bottom,
that's why I advocate
abandoning the entire bottom.
In that case, you're putting me
into a difficult position.
Really, I'm in a dilemma.
You've said this twice.
Let's put this aside.
Tell me where Lemon is.
After all, you lost.
That's true.
Then I'll release all the students
who became puppets.
After all, I lost.
Thank you.
However, you're doing all
this for your mother.
I don't think you are a bad person.
I'm a bit relieved.
Marioness Liberation.
I remember now.
I was captured by a puppet.
Mashle! Lemon!
Great, are you okay?
I'm sorry, I made you worry.
I was really worried.
Thank god you are okay.
What a bunch of fools.
Mother.
Coin, coin, coin…
Hero, hero.
Marry, marry.
-Hero.
-Marry.
I was really scared.
-Thank you, Mashle.
-It's no big deal.
Mashle.
I'm really sorry.
It's all because of me...
But really,
I'm really, really grateful.
I'm glad you're okay.
You are too charming!
What?
I tried hard too.
Ah, Dot.
It's Dot!
Dot.
Wow, wow, wow.
They're all idiots.
Eh, where is Lance?
Eh?
Stop right there.
You're not from this school, are you?
What do you mean...
My magic was dispelled?
The counter's gone off the charts!
How did you find out?
Suspects get punishment, it's
the most convenient way.
What, you fooled me.
I even disguised myself as a student.
Innocent Zero,
an underground dark magic organization.
Why would you rats
come to this school?
Speak up, or I won't let you go.
I came to find something.
Find something?
There's something very,
very important to us.
It should be in this school.
So strange.
DEPRESSED
I let Abel search for it,
but he didn't find anything.
He's just useless.
This is not an answer.
You're so stupid. Why would
I tell you the truth?
I don't know you.
If you want to get
information from anyone,
you have to open them up first.
This is common sense, you know.
No, no.
Now's not the time for this.
I need to get rid of that useless Abel.
Sorry, I don't have time for you.
Next, face the murderer and cannibal,
Jean-Pierre.
Crap.
That guy is probably as strong
as the Divine Visionary.
They might not be able
to compete with him.
Wow, wow, wow.
NEXT EPISODE
(Mashle Burnedead and the Magic Mirror)