Can you imagine a life where you
can't even touch the person you love?
The curse the witch laid upon him caused
him to take the lives of any he touched.
His own mother distanced herself from him,
his friends called him a monster...
Even people he'd never met spoke of him as
"death incarnate that dwells in the forest."
And yet, he doesn't feel
the least bit lonely.
Good morning. Breakfast is ready.
Alice, why don't you take a break?
I'll do the cleaning for once.
But...
Here, just leave it to me.
Where did you pull that out from?
No, I mean, go take a rest!
There's nothing else for me to do.
Then relax!
I know. Don't you have any hobbies?
You're my hobby.
Then something you like?
You're what I like.
O-Oh... huh!
Episode 15
The Duke, Alice, and the Spectral Bride
Listen, Alice. Listen!
The person you love is about
to come out of the next room.
Make sure not to run into them.
Alice!
I'm glad I didn't run into you.
You were in the library this late?
Yeah.
I was really curious
about this business card.
So I was trying to look into what an
octopus could have to do with witches...
But I didn't get anywhere.
Oh, I see.
Will you take a shower?
I haven't taken one myself yet,
so it would be perfect timing.
Why do you think we'd take one together?!
Aw, look at the two of you having fun.
You, know, Alice, I've been wondering...
Do you see them?
See what?
Ghosts!
I felt like maybe you did when that
thing with McFarlane happened.
I do not.
You're lying!
You're just pretending not to
see them so I won't get scared!
You're all I see.
Really?!
I mean, that makes me happy!
But that wasn't what I meant!
I saw you talking by yourself last night...
Do you know anyone who looks like me, then?
Her name would be Sharon.
"Morning! The sun's shining so
bright today! Mommy feels great!"
That's how she talks.
So cute...
I'll be fine. So I want
you to tell me the truth.
Alice, you see ghosts, don't you?
I do not.
You're so stubborn!
I don't see them,
but it's possible that there's been
a ghost in the mansion dressed like
a spectral bride since yesterday.
You do see them, then!
Is she s-saying anything?
Like that she wants revenge
or has unfinished business?
I married the man I loved,
but on the day of the wedding,
this was the ring I got.
I got so mad I lost control of myself,
and then I fell down the stairs and died!
That's a sad way to go.
You're talking with it right now, aren't you?
I don't see them,
but they're usually like that.
You're acting really silly
today, and it's very cute!
How about one of these?
I don't know who they belong to, but they've
been in the mansion for a long time.
There are a lot of different sizes.
She can take the one she likes.
Maybe if she finds the perfect ring,
she'll be able to go to heaven.
Can I really take one?
Yes, if you like it.
You're just talking to a ghost now.
But I don't see them.
He should've measured her ring size.
Perhaps it was a surprise?
Sure, but you can wrap a string around her
finger while she's asleep or something.
What's wrong with these two?
I'm getting jealous.
Lend me your body for a little.
Alice?
Your Grace, I can't control myself anymore.
Maybe there's a spot where
it's safe to touch me.
Why don't we find out together?
N-No!
I don't think I can control myself!
I'm sorry, Alice!
Why did he run away?
My darling's the only one for me.
I'll wait until he's dead.
You'll wait all that time?
Yes. I really do love him.
And looking back, I think
I can forgive him for the ring.
And I need to apologize for dying
so suddenly and leaving him alone.
I guess I made too big a deal out of it.
I'm satisfied now. I'll just move on.
You can have this.
Um, please find happiness.
You too.
Will they come today, you think?
The owner of this business card was
supposed to come in a few days.
That's what Daleth said.
But I need to drive them away when they come!
You're sure?
Well, I'd love to break the curse.
But if I end up owing Daleth a favor
over it, I'll have to do what she wants.
I want you to ask Zain to
use his time magic again.
I promised Zain, so I can't
tell you the details.
But I don't want to cause problems for him.
Don't worry.
No matter what kind of witch
it is, I'll protect you.
How brave.
Let me thank you by...
Keep your clothes on!
Are you psychic?
It seems someone's here.
I-It's time...
Daleth told me to come here.
Is this the place?
U-Um, it's, uh...
Is this your business card?
Oh, great! I finally made it...
W-Water...
Put me in salt water, fast!
Thanks so much!
It's been so long since I've been on land,
and I kind of forgot how it works.
I almost dried up!
I wasn't really thinking
when I saved you but...
You're the witch that's good
with breaking curses, right?
Yes. I'm Amelia.
I'm not so much a witch... as I
am an octopus born with magic.
Daleth told me about you.
A curse that kills just by touching, right?
I've broken a similar curse in the past.
I won't know until I try, but...
I might be able to break it for you!
Um... I hate to say this after
you came all the way here.
But I'm thinking of saying no.
I don't want to owe Daleth anything.
It'll cause problems for a friend of mine.
Humans are always so loyal.
You're such fun creatures!
You've dealt with humans in the past?
Yes. I even married an
unusual man a decade ago.
Married?!
Well, it was only a formality.
I was so bored back then
that I would take the form of a huge octopus
and attack the cargo that ships were carrying.
But one day I attacked an armed pirate ship.
I guess this is it for me.
What is this?
Let me out!
Stay put.
I won't hurt you.
He'd happened to be aboard that day.
He hid me among the other
cargo so I could escape.
Th-Thank you for helping me.
Don't worry about it.
What could be more entertaining
than talking with an octopus witch?
Is that how it works?
You got a boyfriend?
It all happened so fast after that...
We exchanged rings,
though they were cheap ones...
And he went back to the city, and I the sea.
I doubt he remembers, but for me,
it's a wonderful memory.
I've never seen him again,
but I still love him.
That's so romantic!
Right?
I'm not like the pretty
mermaids in the fairy tales!
Who knows what about me he liked?!
She d-disappeared?
No, it's camouflage.
She's changed the color of her
body to match her surroundings.
So we can't see how embarrassed she is?
I know you're bothered by
what Daleth said, but...
I can't promise I'll be
able to break the curse.
Why not let me try before
deciding what you'll do?
But...
Are you that scared of Daleth?
I am!
She's got that scary mask and I can
never tell what she's thinking!
Well, she can be difficult.
She doesn't know how to express herself,
and makes her own life harder.
But she's not a bad girl.
Don't hate her too much.
But she rules the Witches' World!
That's a witch thing.
I'm an octopus. I don't care.
She only ended up ruling because everybody
wanted her to, and she couldn't say no.
First, let's see if we can break your curse.
Or else what did I risk
my life coming here for?
True...
How likely do you think it is
you'll be able to break it?
It depends on how powerful the
witch who laid the curse is.
But from past experience,
I'd say there's an 80% chance.
80%...
If I break the curse, will I be able
to put a ring on Alice's finger?
Of course.
Then please, help me.
If it works, I'll make it
up to Daleth some other way.
Great!
Let's get you turned back into
a normal human right away, then.
Here I go, poor cursed boy.
Don't dodge!
Sorry! Years of habit!
But it's dangerous to touch me!
Witches and octopuses are
both living creatures.
I'm a pro, okay?
A curse clings to the
sufferer's body like a film.
If you want to break the curse,
you just rip it off.
I don't need to touch you.
Want to see my power for yourself?
What? Fish?
The sea is the source of all life.
I can call upon the great
power that dwells in the sea.
I can breathe and talk.
Wow! Is this your magic?
Wow, you're a genius!
Please don't disappear, though!
It makes it hard to compliment you!
Is it alive?
The fish are all so cute!
They're so cute! And so are you!
I'm impressed that you can cry underwater...
Look, Your Grace.
The hallway, too!
And there's a whale outside, too!
My magic covers this whole mansion.
Why not take a walk?
Yay!
He looks like a good kid.
Why was he cursed, I wonder?
I'm looking down at the
mansion... It's so strange.
Look, Alice! There's a
dolphin right next to me!
How cute!
This is fun.
I've never seen fish swimming so close to me.
Me either.
It's like I'm on an undersea date with you.
A-Aw, a date?
Let's walk through the sea together
Let's swim under the sky
A fantastic world beneath shining waves
The fish are dreaming shining dreams
The dolphins, the jellyfish, the sunfish
The angelfish are cute too, but
You're my mermaid after all
I'm not just a maid, I'm your mermaid!
Let's see what's down below, too.
Oh, okay.
A tiger shark!
The pattern is so cute!
And that's an elephant shark next to you!
See how its nose is like an elephant's trunk?
Yes.
It's so strange, seeing all these fish from
different parts of the world in one place.
You know a lot about fish, Your Grace.
Ever since I came here, I've always
been alone when it was time to play.
There wasn't much to do but draw
pictures out of the encyclopedias.
The deep sea fish are all so unique, too.
Yes, it's kind of cute.
Did you have fun?
Yes, a lot!
It was a wonderful time.
I'm glad.
Now, may I get to work?
Yeah. Sorry for getting too excited.
Don't move. Put your hands out.
Okay.
Amelia?
I'm fine.
But what happened in your past?
I can see why Daleth came to me.
I only know of one witch in all of history
who could lay such an evil curse!
Will Amelia be able to break that curse?
Well, I don't expect much.
Zain, don't make a kid
carry such heavy stuff!
I'm carrying more than you!
Don't act like a kid only when it helps you!
Gemini...
The constellation of twins.
Wh-What do you mean?
You know the witch who cursed me?
Just watch.
This is...
The curse placed on you.
Even if I try to rip it off,
it clings right to you.
Amelia, you don't look well...
Its evil power is affecting me.
Don't bother me, Flapjack.
I heard she was dead, but I guess
I still can't break the curse.
Who is this witch?
Sade, Daleth's twin sister.
Sister?
You can't think of any reason she did this?
No!
This is the first time I've
heard Daleth had a twin.
Were the two women in habits that the
logbook spoke of Daleth and Sade?
But what were they doing there that day?
So the reason Daleth wants time
magic has something to do Sade?
Does she want to bring her back to life?
I don't know...
Did I say a little too much?
Daleth will get mad at me.
That curse is more powerful than I am.
I'm sorry, but I don't think I can break it.
How did such a powerful witch die?
I don't know...
The fish...
What's happening?
Amelia?
I'm sorry, I can't keep this up.
Carry me to the sea!
Please!
H-How...?
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
It's okay. I'm sorry we couldn't
do more to welcome you.
I hope you can see your
husband again someday.
Oh, thanks.
Be well, you two.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not sure where to look
when I'm speaking, though.
Hey, Alice.
Let's go see Cuff and Zain soon.
I want to talk to them about Daleth and Sade.
It's rare for you to want to go into town.
If you want tickets to the circus,
Cuff gave me some.
You're putting stuff there again?
When the curse is broken...
I want to go to all kinds of places with you.
I only know what lies beyond
that horizon from books.
I want to see things with my own eyes.
Where do you want to go, Alice?
Hmm... the place I was born,
where I lived with my mother.
I've only got scattered memories of it left,
but there was a big garden,
and my mother taught me
all about flowers there.
I'd love for you to see
it someday, Your Grace.
Let's go, then!
Let's promise!
We can take Rob and Viola, and Cuff and Zain.
I'd love it if Mom, Dad,
and Walter came, too.
Right?
When the curse is broken, we'll all
go to where you grew up together.
It's a promise!
Together...
How happy would I be if I could still
be with you when the curse is broken?
Yes.
Let's promise.
Yeah.
The sea's so cold at night.
Want to get naked and warm each other up?
I'd rather not...
Hey, you're married, right boss?
What's she like?
She's beautiful.
She's easily embarrassed and
likes to hide herself...
And she's got hands this big, and eight legs!
You made the last half of that up!
We've lived apart for 10 years, though.
I miss her...
I'm gonna go clean the toilets.
Don't freak the kid out like that?
Huh?
The Duke of Death and His Maid
The Duke, Alice, and Circus 101
"The Duke, Alice, and Circus 101."