Can you imagine a life where you
can't even touch the person you love?
The curse the witch laid upon him caused
him to take the lives of any he touched.
His own mother distanced herself from him,
his friends called him a monster...
Even people he'd never met
spoke of him as "death incarnate
that dwells in the forest".
And yet, he doesn't feel
the least bit lonely.
Episode 17
Cuff, Zain, and the Confession
Wow!
We're really performing in the middle of town!
I did get permission.
Your Grace...
What do you think of my outfit?
You look fantastic!
But the thought of lots of people
seeing you dressed like that...
I don't know if I like it!
Oh my.
Your Grace.
Wow!
Where's Zain?
Cuff, come with me for a second.
Zain wants to talk to you.
But...
You can't leave Cuff!
I need to talk to her before I go, at least.
Hey, sorry to interrupt you when you're busy.
You're finally going to
tell her you love her?
I know I love her more than you do,
but you've known her for longer than me.
I hate to say it, but you ask her first.
You're right, but you're wrong.
Make sure you make her happy!
I'll kick your ass if you cheat!
Y-You're a good guy!
Okay, I'll leave the two
young people to talk.
Bye!
You're younger than either of us.
Farewell, my first love!
What did you want to talk about?
The show's about to start.
Well, you know.
I realized I'd never really
said thank you for everything.
Thank you.
Where'd that come from?
You're going to go somewhere and
leave me behind, aren't you?
I d-don't know what you're talking about!
I can tell!
Zain...
You're smart.
Following you has never led me astray.
But this time, things are different.
Why didn't you come talk to me?
Forget it!
Do whatever you want!
I'm not your friend anymore!
Wait, Cuff!
No!
Please, listen to me!
Cuff!
I love you.
Why are you saying this now?
Fair point...
But I won't take it back!
I love you! You mean everything to me!
That's why I've decided to leave.
Oh my!
She ran away.
It's starting!
Let's hurry!
It's finally starting.
Are you ready to take off your mask?
Oh, yes.
U-Um, the circus will begin any minute now.
Please stay and watch!
Of course. I will.
It will be an entertaining show, full of chaos.
Uh, thanks?
Cuff?
I'm back...
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
Zain finally told her, huh?
Let's get started.
Ladies and gentlemen...
And today, the younger members
of the audience with us too! Welcome!
The Great Gemini Circus is about to begin!
Wow!
I'm so jealous...
They love it.
And the crowd hated my performance yesterday.
I hope I'll be okay.
Your Grace, I'll teach you a
magic spell to calm your nerves.
A magic spell?
Draw a star on your palm,
and then give someone a hug.
Go ahead.
Don't teach me lies!
But I do feel calmer now, I think.
I'm glad!
Did something happen, Cuff?
Did she find out Zain's leaving?
I'm back.
Wow, I guess the show's already started.
Something must've happened.
Um...
Wow!
What's going on?
Magic's more amazing than any circus.
Right, Teto?
You wanted us to ruin the
circus show, right, Daleth?
That's easy!
Daleth and her friends are here.
They want to ruin the circus
so I can't stay here.
Hugo!
Try and save the kid before he gets digested.
If you do, I'll stab you with
my poison fangs, though.
This show is amazing!
Wouldn't it be smarter to just
come to the Witches' World?
I can't use my magic with
all these people here.
I guess I'll have to use mine, then.
My time magic...
Wow!
It was like magic!
Just try and bite me with your poison fangs!
It'll cost your life!
They loved it!
You're wonderful, Your Grace.
No plant can beat me!
He messed up everything again!
He keeps doing that!
Ringmaster, who were those weirdos?
I don't know, but the crowd's
having the time of their lives!
I guess it's okay, then.
You guys are nuts, too.
I need to do something before
Daleth makes her next move.
Zain, we won't let them ruin the circus.
We'll handle this on our own.
Cuff...
So you don't have to use the magic you hate!
I'll tell you my answer to your
confession after this is all over!
Confession?
Think about how loud you're being!
Where are you hiding, Daleth?
What is it that you see?
Cuff...
I can't see anything at all.
Cuff... Cuff...
Please don't cry.
No matter how many times you try it!
I can keep going with plants
you can't touch directly!
I won't let you interfere anymore!
It's fine! Just stay there!
Okay!
Who's cleaning this up?
Us, I think.
Where are you, Daleth?
My magic can't change fate.
My magic can't protect Cuff!
It's all my fault!
To think he fell for such
a simple illusion...
Zain becomes so weak
whenever Cuff is involved.
It's a good way to buy time, I guess.
Come on out, Daleth!
Why don't I make this even more fun?
Cuff!
Daleth's magic?
Cuff?
Cuff!
Zain!
Don't use your magic!
I can deal with this myself!
Use your magic.
Save me...
Save me!
That's right.
I'm the only one who can protect her smile.
I have to face myself...
And my magic!
Time...
Stop!
Zain?
Did you use your magic to stop time?
No matter what happens from now on,
I'll use my magic to protect you.
You will, huh?
P-Put me down.
Why?
Nobody's looking.
Just a little more...
Put me down! I don't like this!
Okay, now they can't move.
Next is Daleth.
My magic won't last that long.
I don't think we have time to find Daleth.
I'll break the spell, okay?
Wait.
First, can I say something?
This is my answer to your confession!
Cuff kissed me
We're a couple
Yay! Hooray! Yay! Hooray!
Yes!
Now, break the spell.
No, one more time!
Not once more, twice or three times more...
Everybody, the illusion was a success!
Wow!
When did they get over there?
Did Zain stop time?
He's pretty badly hurt...
I bet there was a terrible battle.
That's all for today's show!
Aw, we can keep it up, right?
No, we're packing up!
Let me go!
No, you're my hostages.
You can touch me wherever you want.
I'll let you go.
Do you never learn?
Your Grace, are you hurt?
I'm okay.
What about you?
I'm fine, as you can see.
May we speak for a moment?
Are you Daleth?
You tried to ruin the circus!
That's playing dirty!
I know you need Zain's magic, but...
Forcing Zain to use his magic
helps you two as well.
Especially you, Alice.
I'm going to wake Sharon up from her slumber.
My mother died in an accident long ago.
She did not.
You've never seen her body, have you?
You were just told that
she died in an accident.
Yes, now what was his name?
The man at the mansion...
Do you believe me?
I don't know.
But I would be so happy if it were true.
C-Cuff!
We're even now.
You saw, didn't you?
That scared me!
I see. So Zain and Cuff are...
Good work today!
Today's big show was a lot of fun!
This is the first time I've seen
a real bar! Not just a picture!
I told you you'd be a big hit.
Today was the first time
anybody's wanted my autograph.
I got scared and ran off, though.
That's just like you, Your Grace.
By the way...
Zain and Cuff, are you two witches?
Wh-What?
I thought so.
It explains a lot about
today and everything else.
You two are so cool!
You should've said something before!
Is that all?
I feel like an idiot for keeping it a secret.
And shouldn't you be trying to get rid of us?
We might cause problems
for you like we did today!
If you want to cause
problems for us, then fine.
We cause problems for you.
That's right.
You have good friends.
Yeah.
We're not friends.
We're family.
Family, huh?
Speaking of family, my wife's a witch.
And an octopus, actually.
An octopus?
You mean Amelia?
You know my wife?
Yeah, she helped me out with my curse.
Is she doing well?
Yes!
I see...
Glad to hear that.
It explains a lot if you're her husband.
Yeah?
Well, enough about me.
Zain and Cuff have something to say, right?
Yeah...
Actually...
Congratulations!
Another toast, to our new lovers!
Cheers.
Cheers!
Now give me a kiss!
Oh, right.
About your curse.
Think of it as a trial that God's placed
before you. One you can overcome.
Don't get too worked up about it.
I can overcome it...?
After it's broken, you'll give
me that handshake.
I promise!
Thanks for coming.
Thanks so much.
Should we hug, too?
No, I'll pass.
Bye!
I'm sure Rob's waiting up for us.
Yes.
Don't ever try and leave me again, okay?
The Duke of Death and His Maid
Cuff, Zain, and the Confession
"The Duke and Everyone's Daily Life."