Can you imagine a life where you
can't even touch the person you love?
The curse the witch laid upon him caused
him to take the lives of any he touched.
His own mother distanced herself from him.
His friends called him a monster.
Even people he'd never met spoke of him as
"Death Incarnate who dwells in the forest."
And yet, he doesn't feel
the least bit lonely.
How many times do we have to go over this?
You can't have an omelet without ketchup.
It's demi-glace sauce.
Why? 'Cause demi-glace sauce tastes good.
So does ketchup!
You guys are lucky. You can tell each
other exactly how you're feeling.
I'm jealous.
Huh? If you want to say something
to Alice, then why don't you say it?
Hmm? But I'm not really
upset with her or anything.
Excuse me.
Alice...
Stop being so cute all the time!
You're so handsome all the time, too.
That wasn't what I expected
to hear, but I'll take it!
Go home!
I guess this is your house, though.
Episode 14
The Duke, Golf, and the Mysterious Beauty
Oh, Your Grace.
It's your first time, but you're so good.
Would you try not to sound so weirdly sexy?
I'm just playing mini-golf!
You're wonderful, Your Grace.
I missed.
You hit it a little too hard, I see.
Why golf, though?
I thought it would serve to fix your lack
of exercise, and give you a change of pace.
I just wanted to play with you, Your Grace.
So cute!
Let's not worry about the rules.
Just aim for the flag and hit it.
That motion has nothing to do with golf!
Wow!
Is there anything you can't do?
Perhaps I'm good at it because
it's like sweeping with a broom.
I'll show you the trick, if you like.
Yes, please.
Eyes on the ball, and don't look up.
It will send your swing off target.
Okay.
Your Grace.
What?
Don't turn around. Just look at the ball.
When we're so close, it makes me
feel kind of hot. What about you?
You're the one who got close to me!
Don't tell me she's stripping!
That's not where the ball goes, Your Grace...
This is a living hell!
Golf is a scary sport!
Now try hitting it.
Don't try to swing hard or soft.
Just raise the club up and swing
it through evenly.
For instance, if you raised it this high,
swing it through that much.
Not only did I not get that,
she was flirting with me as
casually as if she was breathing.
Imagine a clock. If you raised it
to 7 o' clock, swing to 5 'o clock.
Or 9 to 3.
Or 12 to 12.
Okay. I wouldn't swing a
putter that hard, though.
Don't look up. Focus on the ball.
Swing it through as much as you raised it up!
I did it!
Wonderful, Your Grace.
Yeah, it's so nice to learn something new!
Hole in One!
All I'm doing is putting a ball into a hole
So why, so why, is golf so much fun?
Your bold approach
Tee shot, make some tea
It fell into the lake!
You're so great, Your Grace!
Golf, golf, let's all fall in love with golf
You want me to dress up like a girl?
No, I want to practice makeup on your face!
You know, Mom won't let me do my own makeup.
And I don't want to ask the maids.
Sure, if you want.
That's my big brother, Walter!
He's a nut, but he gets me!
That doesn't sound like a compliment at all.
All right, now let's get to work on your face!
First the foundation, then some eyeliner...
Add a wig, and then change your clothes...
And we're done!
Look! Look!
Impossible...
This is me?!
Don't start taking a liking to it.
Hey, why don't you go to the villa
and show it to my dear brother?
To the eldest?
I'll do it!
Because today, I am super-cute!
I'll make him fall in love with
me and tell Mother all about it!
And then I shall become the heir!
He's such a scumbag.
Bam!
I call it... Project Honeytrap!
Now hurry and get ready to go, Viola!
Before my cuteness fades!
Well, this should be fun, at least!
Ha ha! I'm so cute!
I guess that one was too weak.
Golf's hard.
You're getting better, Your Grace.
I am?
There you are, Dear Brother!
Viola and... who?
Our new maid!
She says she's a fan of yours, so I brought her.
A fan? Of me?
That's right!
She was all, "A curse?! That's so cool!
He's totally my type!"
Oh, I see.
But why doesn't she talk?
She's too nervous to talk!
The fool has no idea what
I've got in store for him!
Kneel in awe before me!
Initiate Project Honeytrap!
Stare at me! Come on! Stare!
What's going on?
Most men would react more if a
girl flashed her legs, right?
Is he some kind of psychopath?
She started showing me her legs, too.
Is that just a maid thing?
Okay, I'll go find Rob!
You three have fun!
Wait, Viola!
She abandoned me already!
This is hilarious!
Continue feeling awkward, Brothers!
U-Um... want to play some golf?
I'll go first, then.
Is it true that she's a fan of mine?
It doesn't sound possible.
His skills are nothing special.
If seduction won't work, I'll need
to think of something else!
His Grace looks so sexy playing golf!
Um, you want to go second?
Second?!
You can have my second putter.
And my second ball.
Second?!
Sound good?
Second!
He's always like this!
From the very bottom of his heart,
he mocks me for being the second son!
Um, you okay?
I'm okay.
"If I get a hole in one,
please go out with me"?
Wh... Wh... What?
Well?
You may not know me well, but it must
make you happy to hear that from a girl!
Distance is 30.
No wind. Oaken floor.
"Please marry me like you promised"?
Marry you? I didn't promise that!
"It's the same."
"Let's have the ceremony immediately."
"Prepare yourself."
N-No...
Let's have the
ceremony immediately.
Prepare yourself.
No.
No!
I'm sorry.
I forgot my place.
She's so cute.
She pulled it over her head...
Um, I'm sorry if I'm just
being arrogant here...
But there's someone I'm in love with,
so I can't give you what you want.
I'm willing to be friends, though.
Die!
Farewell!
Aah!
Her voice kind of sounded like Walter.
Did it?
Perhaps I wasn't cute enough.
Will you instruct me further
in the Viola Method?
Nope!
Don't stare so much, Zain. I'm practicing.
What's the problem? You're good!
Don't! You're distracting me!
Cuff! I brought you juice!
She's practicing.
Scram, kid. Cuff doesn't like sweet stuff.
I love juice!
And I love you, Cuff.
Careful. He might've put
something weird in it.
I did not!
Stop acting like her boyfriend!
You're not dating, right?
We're childhood friends.
That's right.
"Cuff said no so fast
It hurt Zain's feelings really bad
Now he feels blue
5-7-5, but not quite"
Thanks, Hugo.
I'll work hard!
I'll be a big man for you, Cuff.
You're funny.
I know Cuff only sees Hugo as a kid.
But I really do not like this!
You need to win the heart of your precious
Cuff soon, or Hugo might take her!
Ringmaster?
The customers will be
here soon. Head backstage.
We'll start the show like always.
O-Okay.
You've got it rough, Cuff.
Not at all. Every day is fun.
I love the circus!
Everyone is always so happy.
Glad to hear it.
The circus is the best
entertainment there is.
All are welcome, both as
performers and guests.
That's why I don't care who you
are, and I won't ask questions.
But it sounds like a fun story, so I'm curious.
Tell me any time you feel like it, I guess.
The show's about to start.
Thanks to all your work,
we've got a packed house today.
Fun. Fascinating. But safety first.
Stay sharp out there.
Yes, sir!
Win her heart, he said?
I just can't find the right time to say it...
If we stay here in the human world,
somebody's going to find out
we're witches eventually.
Should I just disappear and leave her behind?
No, but...
I don't care if I'm a human or
a witch... as long as I'm with you.
You scared?
Don't worry. You've got me,
the great Cuff, by your side!
She has no idea what I'm going through.
Sure, she is cute, but...
If you're scared...
You can always hold my hand.
If she's that embarrassed,
then she shouldn't have offered.
It's time.
Cuff, Zain, you okay?
It's a "l-let's do our best" handshake!
I'm such a wimp.
Tea is ready, Your Grace.
Yeah, thanks.
Where am I?
Excuse me. Is this seat taken?
You're... Daleth?
I summoned you because
I have something to discuss.
The real you is unconscious
in the room you were just in.
Your Grace?
Is it my curse you wanted to talk about?
That's part of it, but first
I have a favor I wanted to ask.
You see...
Something feels weird...
It seems Alice is concerned
and poking your cheek.
She is?
Your Grace?
Not the neck, Alice!
That tickles!
S-Sorry.
It's nice how close you two are.
Well, whatever.
I want you to try and
persuade someone for me.
Persuade?
Just as you humans all
excel at different things,
we witches all have magic we excel at.
Be it controlling fire or
causing plants to grow...
Those are the more common types, of course.
I'm looking for a witch whose
powers are more advanced.
A witch with the power
to control time itself.
From the look on your face,
you know who I'm referring to.
Yes. Zain is a magical genius.
But for some reason, he hides it.
If it weren't for the incident with the
logbook, I couldn't have been sure.
She knew...
And that's why I want you to ask
him to use his time magic again.
He's so nice... He'd do
anything a friend asked.
How about it?
I can't do that.
I don't know about his magic.
And I certainly can't if there's
some reason he doesn't use it.
Well, I thought you'd say that.
He's your friend. I understand.
But if you can do what I ask...
I'm willing to break your curse.
You can't sleep?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
We've got another performance tomorrow.
Get to sleep soon.
I will.
Childhood friends...
I've heard you're the child
of a witch and a human!
I'm Zain. What's your name?
I won't give you my name until you
apologize for throwing that rock.
I'm sorry.
I'm Cuff.
Nice to meet you.
My parents sent me to live
in the human world so that
other witches wouldn't try to abuse my power.
But...
I still didn't understand the
power of the magic I had.
It's just barely alive... but it's
going to wilt at this rate.
Leave it to me.
I'll use my magic to fix it.
Magic?
It came back to life!
It's easy, as long as you have my time magic!
Wow! You're a genius!
Yeah! It's a secret to everybody, though!
I can do this, too!
I stopped time and moved.
Wow!
I know what color your panties are, too!
They're white with strawberries on them!
You stopped time and looked, huh?
Cuff called me a genius.
We became friends and played every day.
But one day while we were out playing,
our parents were found
by human witch-hunters.
Cuff, don't cry! I'll use my time
magic to bring them back to life!
Can you do that?
Of course I can! I'm Zain, the magical genius!
I wanted to see her smile.
But...
Even magic that can control time
can't bring the dead back to life.
I'm sorry, Cuff. I couldn't
save them with my magic.
Time can't change fate.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry...
Don't say you're sorry...
Don't say you're sorry, Zain.
Ever since that day, I've hated my magic.
I couldn't even protect Cuff's smile.
Break my curse? What does that mean?
Did you curse me in the first place after all?
Don't get the wrong idea.
What I said before was the truth.
The witch who cursed you
is gone from this world.
All I can do is...
What is this?
I called a witch I know who
excels at breaking curses.
I don't know if they'll succeed,
but it gives you hope, right?
They'll arrive in a few days.
When they're done, do me that favor, please.
Wait! You can't do this!
Tell me! Why do you need
magic that controls time?
Who are you?
At least let me see your face!
No. I'm ugly.
Alice! That's dangerous!
Oh, Your Grace. You hadn't woken up,
so I was going to do CPR.
The second you tried, you'd go to sleep forever!
R-Right! Daleth told me she
needed me to do something!
She said a witch is coming!
Calm down, Your Grace.
Is that a business card?
An octopus?
Why an octopus?
The Duke of Death and His Maid
The Duke, Alice, and the Spectral Bride
"The Duke, Alice, and the Spectral Bride."