Abyss Razor.
From now on,
I will give meaning to that eye of yours.
From today, you'll be my tool.
Follow me.
Lord Abel.
(Mashle: Magic and Muscle)
Just as Mashle and his friends
defeated the Magia Lupus…
How is Mashle doing now?
He didn't cause a huge commotion
by revealing that he
can't use magic, did he?
That guy must become a Divine Visionary.
Otherwise, I'll be in trouble.
This is also for my own plans.
Don't you have work?
What's more important?
Work or making an appearance?
Making an appearance is indeed important.
Yeah, I agree.
Would you like another cup of tea?
Hmm.
Let me introduce this again.
This story is about
Mashle Burnedead, who has no magic power,
and his experience
in Easton Magic Academy
before he becomes a Divine Visionary…
They're still celebrating here!
Protagonist! Protagonist! Protagonist!
Heroine! Heroine!
I'm the heroine!
-Are you the hero?
-Oh yeah.
How long will they keep celebrating?
Ah, can I go to the restroom?
He must have wanted to go long ago.
Well, I guess this is the end.
Yeah.
The students who turned into dolls
have all restored to human form.
But the security at
this school is really bad.
The thrill can also
stimulate our love though.
What are you talking about?
By the way, where's that pretty boy?
He didn't lose, did he?
I don't think Lance would lose.
Hmm? That was fast…
Who are you?
Don't get in my way.
Ouch, what are you doing?
Why are you all battered?
Did you lose?
You can't even be the strongest
student in this school?
How embarrassing.
However, I'm still grateful to you.
Thank you for collecting information
about Principal Wahlberg.
My… arms…
The searching didn't go very well,
but in fact,
you don't have a reason to exist
-anymore.
-So
let's have orange juice and
cream puffs for the celebration.
Why's there a brat who
can't read the atmosphere?
Huh? The vibe feels a bit strange.
No, Mashle.
Now is not the time for that.
Where did he get the cream puffs from?
Is this a coincidence?
Or is it on purpose?
I'm very sorry.
I still want to eat that.
Can you give it back to me?
He still wants to eat that cream puff?
SHOCKED
You are such a rude guy.
What's with this headache?
Could it be… resonance?
But,
I didn't have a headache
when I first came here.
Is it because of
this guy who just came in?
Uh, this guy…
Ah, this guy is the one
we're looking for…
Forget it.
I'll go ahead with the plan
and kill Abel first.
It's useless.
The difference in our abilities as Mages
is too great.
Die.
Abyss!
Masked guy!
I'm sorry, Mashle.
I'm afraid I can't
have cream puffs with you anymore.
Take this.
Magic handkerchief.
My attack didn't cause a fatal injury.
That mushroom head
threw a stone at me at that moment,
causing the magic trajectory to deviate.
It's him.
Are you Abel's dog? Quite active, huh?
An adopted social scourge
returning the favor?
You make me sick.
He stepped on the ground…
He caught it!
What?
You are quite rebellious.
Then you can die with him.
Eh, why are you licking the stone?
Is that what people your age do?
Whatever.
I'm taking masked guy to the hospital now.
If you dare stop me, I'll beat you up.
Beat me up?
Not bad.
He still has thirty minutes.
Can you really save him
in the time he has left?
What?
Didn't you say you were
going to beat me up?
Seems like you're all talk.
I can't win against him.
The difference in our
talent is too great.
Talent…
My mother often told me,
we
just happened to be born into privilege.
Background, talent,
appearance, all these things.
We just got them by
being luckier than others.
So…
Don't space out, Abel!
Carbon rain!
It's no use.
We are at an absolute disadvantage now.
We can't win against him.
Stupid Abyss.
There was no need
to protect me.
I think he used to be very happy.
He was always lonely.
It was hard enough for him to survive.
So,
when he knew you needed him,
he must have been very happy.
And I share his feelings.
So
I will save you.
The masked guy must want
to eat cream puffs too.
We just happened to
be born into privilege.
Background, talent, appearance,
we got these by chance.
So, Abel,
you should think from
other people's perspectives.
That way,
you'll be gentler to others.
That's right, gentle.
Be gentler to others.
Haven't you given up yet?
Carbon rain!
Lord Abel.
Abyss.
Ah, it's the Evil Eye! Run!
Don't come near me!
I wish I hadn't given birth to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry I was
born into this world.
I heard about it.
You have the Evil Eye.
I'm sorry, I'll try to avoid
eye contact with you.
You don't need to hide.
Can your eye be of use to me?
I wouldn't dare.
If you use this eye,
you'll be ostracized by
those around you too.
That doesn't matter.
From now on, I'll give meaning
to that eye of yours.
From today, you'll be my tool.
Follow me.
Please… please,
please run away.
You just say nice things.
Be it my mother
or Abyss.
Carbon rain!
Have you used up all your
strength just blocking my attack?
Pathetic, how pathetic.
If you don't hurry, he'll die.
Mashle.
Not good.
Those carbon-like solids
are hard and numerous.
Although Mashle is moving
forward little by little,
there's not enough time
for him to reach the opponent.
That being said,
if I go to help Mashle,
these two will be in danger.
I can't help him.
I'm fed up.
Carbon Heavy Rain!
He has even more advanced magic!
Damn it! Even if I could help,
it might be too late.
Should I go help him?
Damn it!
Mashle.
The exploitation of the weak by the strong
is a natural right.
But,
resisting the strong
is also the natural right of the weak.
What do you want to do, Abel?
I want to verify what's right
with my own hands.
Hmm, is that so?
Carbon Heavy Rain!
Unfortunately,
you can't win with this level of magic…
Hello.
This is the first time
someone has been able
to break my hard shell.
Although it was a sneak attack.
What magic did you use?
I'm asking what your personal magic is.
Uh, I…
Power.
Power?
Is there such magic?
I see you're not planning to tell me.
Fine, it doesn't matter.
That is…
The Anti-Magic Mirror!
A magical tool that reflects
any magic attack.
That is to say,
the stronger the opponent's magic,
the more powerful the mirror becomes.
It's the most feared
magical tool by all Mages!
It should be under the Bureau's control.
Why…
Stop it, Mashle!
That's something we Mages
absolutely cannot confront.
The magic you cast will
be reflected on yourself!
One wrong step and
you'll be in grave danger!
To confront that thing,
you have to break through
it in a non-magical way.
But that's…
Because you got in my way,
I'll make all of you regret it.
Come on, use your magic,
as long as you don't mind rotting
in your own magical power.
Can you do it…
Magic…
This is not magic!
So, back then…
And then…
And now too!
That is to say, all those things
he did weren't magic.
Mashle did it solely by his own body…
Is this really possible?
Isn't that strange?
This has become a fantasy story, right?
Isn't it a fantasy story?
It's already a fantasy story, this…
Completely ineffective!
Did it appear the moment
I made contact with that brat?
If it's just the headache from earlier…
As expected, it's this guy.
Is it?
What is that!
Today, I had an unexpected reward.
Because I met you.
My name is Cell War.
INNOCENT ZERO CELL WAR
I have urgent matters,
so I'll be leaving now.
But I think we'll meet again soon.
Bye bye.
He really left like he said.
I'm really grateful.
Come on, let's take masked
guy to the hospital.
You don't have to worry about that.
Thanks to the handkerchief you gave me.
He's alright now.
Next time,
you have to treat me
to cream puffs, okay?
Masked guy.
I'll get Abyss to the hospital.
I want to thank you, Mashle Burnedead.
I'll definitely return this favor.
This thing is finally over.
Ah, it's not!
Everything you've done
till now isn't magic?
That's even more amazing.
It'll get you into trouble
if anyone else finds out.
You'll be in trouble, Mashle.
You might be expelled because of that.
No… that… that is magic.
He looks so nervous.
Is there a reason in it?
Anyway,
we need to keep his secret
to protect him from the others.
That's right.
If Mashle gets into trouble,
it'll also damage our marriage.
For now, let's hide Mashle
before taking the next steps.
Thank you, guys.
He actually said thank you.
I didn't expect us to be unanimous.
No, it seems things have gotten worse.
If his secret gets exposed,
we'll definitely face consequences.
We'll also be expelled.
No!
I heard everything.
A person who can't use
magic is in this school.
That's something serious.
I'm going to report you to the professor.
What… it's over.
The students turned into puppets…
They've all regained consciousness.
A student who can't use magic
is in a magic school.
Report, report, report!
DEPRESSED
This moment has finally come.
He's not affected at all.
The fact that Mashle can't use magic
has finally been exposed.
What do you do, Mashle?
Your happy life with your Pop
is in danger now!
Father,
I'm sorry that this took some time.
I finally found
the thing we lost.
You did? Finally…
My longtime wish is about to come true.
Go and catch him.
(Mashle: Magic and Muscle)
(The Divine Visionary Candidates Selection Exam)
TV ANIME SEASON 2
SCHEDULED TO AIR IN JANUARY 2024