<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14013" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-09-18</startdate>
<enddate>2020-09-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Violet Evergarden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">violet movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 ヴァイオレット・エヴァーガーデン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Violet Evergarden the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Violet Evergarden: Il Film</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">극장판 바이올렛 에버가든</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Violet Evergarden: O Filme</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">劇場版 紫羅蘭永恆花園</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">剧场版 紫罗兰永恒花园</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12138" type="Prequel">Violet Evergarden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="834921">The conclusion for an already highly acclaimed anime. Genuinely made me cry. Not a standalone film.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="129389">The brain may tell you that this is vapid, saccharine and by the numbers, the way it understands that candy is unhealthy. Nevertheless, candy is still enjoyable, and Japan demonstrates its mastery of visual candymaking very convincingly here indeed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="326899">For once Violet made me think about my own love, my weeknseses, my longing for something grate. And made me cry, true tearjerker this is. Almost like Nana which rendered me a crybaby for hours.

Highly recomended, but please watch the series beforehand.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="531127">It`s not possible to watch this movie and keep your heart like a stone. It moves your feelings and sentiments! Violet Evergarden is one of the most beautiful, powerful and emotional movie I`ve ever seen before. What an amazing and exciting ending for this series. 

If you are a fan of the previous tv series, the special chapter and the other movie, you definitely have to see this jewel. On the other hand, if you are new by here I promise you will fall in love with and then you will have to watch all of the Violet Evergarden universe.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://violet-evergarden.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="47074" type="Character Design">Takase Akiko</name>
<name id="45939" type="Original Work">Akatsuki Kana</name>
<name id="532" type="Direction">Ishidate Taichi</name>
<name id="47074" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takase Akiko</name>
<name id="39819" type="Music">Evan Call</name>
</creators>
<description>While writing other people`s emotions, she may have neglected her own. http://anidb.net/ch89959 [Violet Evergarden], the child soldier turned Auto Memory Doll, writes letters that evoke the words her clients can`t. But when a terminally ill http://anidb.net/ch114874 [boy] requests her services for his family, her own feelings about love and loss resurface. Now she must confront her past and the death of the http://anidb.net/ch90198 [Major].
Source: funimation</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="753">8.90</permanent>
<temporary count="759">8.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>245073.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22376</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37987</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://violet-evergarden.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Violet_Evergarden:_The_Movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヴァイオレット・エヴァーガーデン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363980</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22470</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Violet_Letter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="41">
<externalentity>
<identifier>81193214</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="43">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tt8652818</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7885" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-11-07">
<name>Japanese production</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89959" type="main character in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="218">8.96</rating>
<name>Violet Evergarden</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="276855.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90197" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="42">6.67</rating>
<name>Cattleya Baudelaire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90198" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="14">4.92</rating>
<name>Gilbert Bougainvillea</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90199" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="22">5.92</rating>
<name>Claudia Hodgins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="11010.jpeg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90200" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="18">4.81</rating>
<name>Benedict Blue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="264505.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92846" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-16">
<rating votes="19">3.59</rating>
<name>Iris Cannary</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92847" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-10">
<rating votes="22">3.12</rating>
<name>Erica Brown</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93414" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-01">
<rating votes="12">3.19</rating>
<name>Dietfried Bougainvillea</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dietfried Bougainvillea is a naval captain in the navy and http://anidb.net/ch90198 [Gilbert]`s older brother. He was the one who found http://anidb.net/ch89959 [Violet] and made her into Gilbert`s "weapon" on his promotion to a major in the army.
Source: Violet Evergarden Wiki</description>
<picture>217048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="265956.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="114873" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-01-19">
<rating votes="2">5.39</rating>
<name>Daisy Magnolia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>256001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="114874" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-01-19">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Julis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>255999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="114875" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-01-19">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Lucas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>256000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="215682" update="2020-09-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>140</length>
<airdate>2020-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="248397" update="2021-10-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">公開記念舞台挨拶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Premiere Commemoration Stage Greeting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukai Kinen Butai Aisatsu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
