How...
did this happen?
Death Incarnate dwells in the forest.
He takes the life of whatever he touches.
That was the curse the witch put on him.
Why did the witch curse him?
How can the curse be broken?
The answer remains hidden.
And yet, he doesn't feel
the least bit lonely.
Episode 13
The Duke, Alice, and the Magic Pool
Your Grace.
Alice, you scared me!
You're too close! But I guess
you're always too close.
I knocked, but there was no answer.
Oh, yeah?
I guess I was focusing.
A card tower?
You're quite good with your hands.
The way you were panicking a moment ago,
I assumed you were by yourself because you
didn't want me to see what you were doing.
What's that supposed to mean?
You have no idea at all?
No! So stay away from me!
You'll die if you touch me!
I couldn't help myself.
The way you reacted was so cute.
Be careful!
If you died, I'd die too.
Why?
Why? Because I love you.
Oh my. That's even cuter, Your Grace.
I want Alice to think I'm cool, not cute!
Just watch! I'll do something
awesome to impress her!
Well, she's certainly watching.
I want to concentrate on placing the cards.
Can you hand them to me?
Of course,
Your Grace.
Don't put them there!
I'll put some here, too.
I can't concentrate at all!
I love seeing you so serious.
Please, just let me focus!
I know I've got more important
things I should be doing.
My mother gave me that time limit.
Yes.
You must break your curse
by spring at the latest.
I don't like it, but...
In her own way, she'd been
waiting for me this whole time.
I want to make her happy.
Honestly, I'd be fine with
Walter becoming the next heir.
If you cannot, then I shall
make Walter the heir.
Of course, I want to break the curse,
and not because I want to be heir.
Cuff and Zain are helping me.
More than anything, I want to do it for you.
Your Grace...
Alice!
Have you enjoyed this night
filled with mystery and wonder?
This concludes tonight's
Circus Gemini performance.
The crowd loved you, Cuff!
Tonight's show was so cool!
I never would've had this much
fun if I'd stayed a pickpocket!
Thanks for inviting me here, Cuff!
You should thank the Ringmaster
for inviting you here.
Just you wait.
I'll get even better at my tricks
and become a big-time man who's worthy of you!
Hugo, you are far too young
to be trying to seduce girls.
Let me go, Zain!
Or I'll rip that weird
mask right off your face!
I'd like to see you try—
Ow! Ow!
Ringmaster!
He's bothering me! Make him go away!
Sure.
It's past your bedtime, kid.
Do you all pick me up the same way?
Why do you all pick me up the same way?
I'm glad you guys came.
The audience loves you.
Night.
Damn it!
Cuff, good night!
Zain, go screw yourself!
See you tomorrow!
Right, good night!
That kid might not like me,
but he's a hard worker.
He said he wants to work
here and support his family.
Yup. He was only stealing because
he didn't have a choice.
This is the first time I've ever been
given a flower. I think I like it!
Well...
I'll get you a flower too, then!
One this big!
Oh, uh, thanks.
Hey, Cuff.
How long are we going to stay here?
It's close to Alice and the Duke, and nobody
asks questions about how I look, but...
We need to get out of here before
they find out we're witches.
I don't want to cause
problems for the circus.
But... I don't want to leave this place.
Oh, right! I just remembered something!
Last time I went to the Witches' World,
I swiped some magic items
while Daleth wasn't looking.
You're no better than Hugo.
They were just sitting in an
old storeroom. Nobody will notice.
And...
Daleth owes me.
She hasn't let me fondle
even one of her boobs!
And what?
No, nothing!
Here.
Look at all this stuff!
Let's take them with us next time
we go see Alice and the Duke!
One of them might help break his curse!
What do you want to live as?
A witch or a human?
If you don't use your magic,
you can pass as a human.
You've got friends here.
You wouldn't be alone.
And it would be less dangerous
than staying with me.
I'm cold. Let me inside your jacket.
I don't care if I'm a human or
a witch... as long as I'm with you.
Oh. I see.
Boobs!
Emptiness
Her boobs are touching me!
G Cup!
Every time I see it, I want it more.
The magic to control time...
You agree, don't you, Sharon?
There you are, Viola.
I'm glad you're still here. I thought
you might've gone to see the eldest son.
If I want to go, that's my choice, right?
Mother never told me I couldn't.
That's our grandfather and grandmother.
Yes.
I know it's a painting, but still,
every time I see her, I can't
help but think how cute she is.
I can see why Grandfather
was so in love with her.
Yes.
She died in a carriage accident
shortly after Father was born.
And he never remarried.
He was probably so lonely.
Perhaps I'm starting to see things...
Sorry to interrupt!
Cuff?
Was I really interrupting?
No, not at all!
It's been a while.
The circus has been so busy lately
that I haven't been able to drop by.
We're just glad you came.
We can't really go into town.
I love it here 'cause I can
use all the magic I want!
You'll burn the mansion down!
Don't worry! These flames are magic,
and do whatever I want!
When they disappear, they leave
nothing behind at all!
Well, that's okay, then.
But it's really hot in here now...
Right?
It's like the middle of summer, right?
So let's take a dip in the pool!
Pool?
I recognize this design.
Zain brought it from the Witches' World.
Now that I've heated up the room,
we can enjoy the pool even though
it's the middle of winter!
He even chose our swimsuits!
You sure can tell what he likes...
So, where is he?
Oh, he's...
Listen carefully, Cuff.
When you go swimming with
Alice in your swimsuits,
make sure you invite me!
It's dangerous for two girls
to be in the water alone!
You need me to keep watch!
You need me, okay?!
I left him at home.
Anyway, Alice, let's get in the pool.
It's so hot!
All right, just a moment.
What are you doing?
It's so hot in here, I thought I'd take
off my clothes before getting my swimsuit.
Get the swimsuit first!
Both of you, please change in another room!
I already changed, though.
That was fast!
I can't look...
And Alice is right here.
I'll go change in my room, then.
I have returned.
She's so cute...
You had your own swimsuit, then.
Yes.
I assumed I'd get a chance
to show it to you someday.
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
You're not getting in the pool?
I'll pass.
You two have fun.
You can sit there and watch us...
all you like.
Okay...
The water feels so good.
Whee! Splash!
Alice is so pretty.
Zain is gonna be so mad later.
It's not fair!
Hey, Cuff.
You said you've been busy with the circus.
Do the people there know you're a witch?
No, I don't think they do.
Why did you join the circus, anyway?
Well...
You guys ever thought
about joining the circus?
We don't get a lot of customers,
but every day is fun!
The place is always on the verge
of bankruptcy, but it's a nice place.
Lately we've had more customers, so it's busy.
I'd love to go see you some day.
Right, Alice?
Yes.
Any time! We'd always be happy to see you!
Kyah!
Kyah! Kyah! Kyah!
She's so cute...
Now it's your turn to splash
me as hard as you can!
We can have a splash fight!
Of course.
You're so nice...
What are you doing?
I thought I could help you feel
like you're on a tropical island.
It's not just the piano. You can paint, too.
Thanks.
Oh no... It's a little too hot.
I'm getting dizzy.
Your Grace.
You seem hot. Why don't you join us?
The water is cold and feels so good.
No, I... I don't like baring my skin.
Oh no!
Alice, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I need to make sure I'm staying hydrated.
It's hot. We need to be careful.
I've started to turn red myself.
That was so much fun!
I'm heading home, but you guys can have that.
Th-Thanks.
And this is from Zain.
A box? What's inside?
He didn't say.
I randomly grabbed a bunch of stuff!
So I'll have him try them out for me!
That's what he said.
Am I his guinea pig?
Perhaps it's part of a series?
Yeah, probably.
"Sweet dreams."
What does it do, I wonder?
Something they use in the Witches'
World to help them sleep, perhaps?
That would definitely be a nightmare.
Well, Zain gave it to me.
It can't be that dangerous.
Rustle, rustle, rustle...
Pop!
Oh?
It's empty?
Your Grace?
What is this place?
Welcome, Your Grace.
Alice? Why are you dressed like that?
I'm a bunny girl.
No, I get that, but...
In this place, your wishes become real.
M-My wishes?
I see.
So this will allow me to see
into your fantasies, then.
Alice?
No, this is...
You like bunny girls, then?
I'll get you for this, Zain!
Since this world is a fantasy,
is it safe to touch His Grace?
Of course.
Would you like to touch me, Young Master?
I'll just watch.
Please, no!
O-Oh, what's behind that door?
Oh, this?
It contains more of your fantasies.
I'll show you around.
D-Do I have to go?
I've got the feeling Alice might see
something even more embarrassing...
I'm very curious.
I want to see, too.
We agree, then.
You're the same person!
Let's just go.
Oh, look at all of me!
I'm so s-sorry.
There's nothing to apologize for.
Something like this is healthy, actually.
I'm feeling nothing but
shame and embarrassment.
Why am I being forced to suffer like this?
I'm quite enjoying it.
I need to write down what
you like before I forget.
Please no!
Okay, next.
Dear Brother!
Viola?
Um, there's something on this
music sheet I can't read.
Tell me what this means again!
"Allegretto. Moderately fast,
slower than allegro."
Thank you!
You're so amazing, Dearest Brother!
I'm so proud to be your little sister!
Is this a fantasy, too?
Yeah, and it's making me sad.
Let's keep going.
Wow...
If I could play the piano
in a place like this...
It would be so much fun, I'm sure.
Will you play, then?
I can?
Yes. This is your fantasy, after all.
That was wonderful, Your Grace.
Thank you.
Did you enjoy that?
Yeah.
I know it's just my own fantasy, though.
This is a wonderful world.
Let's look around a little more.
Um, Alice, I'd rather call it a night...
I want to see the depths of your desire.
That's a really scary thing to say!
A-Alice, what did you see?
Your Grace, I didn't know you
imagined me looking like that.
Wait, what?
There's more?
Now, let's get going.
H-Hold it! What did you see? Alice? Alice!
I'll show you to the exit.
I loved playing the piano,
but this box is scary.
Zain, why did you give me this?
I'll put this away.
Yeah. Make sure you lock it up tight.
It did make me happy, though.
The Duke of Death and His Maid
The Duke, Golf, and the Mysterious Beauty
"The Duke, Golf, and the Mysterious Beauty."