[metal screeching and clanking]
[ominous, unsettling music playing]
[metronome ticking]
[music intensifies]
[Carl] Are you ready?
We're ready.
Ready to forget once and for all.
Good, Mr Lambert.
So then, close your eyes.
Both of you.
Now take a deep breath.
Now feel yourselves getting sleepier
and sleepier.
Neither of you will remember
the last year.
There is no place called The Further.
[ticking slows]
You will only remember Dalton's coma.
And his recovery.
And let the darkness drift further...
and further away.
[ominous music playing]
[Dalton]
For everything, there is a season.
A time to be born...
and a time to die.
A time to kill...
a time to heal.
A time to keep...
and a time to throw away.
A time to weep...
and a time to laugh.
A time to mourn, and a time to dance.
A time for silence...
and a time to speak.
A time for love...
and a time to hate.
A time for war, and a time for peace.
Amen.
[all] Amen.
[woman] We therefore commit this body
to the ground.
Earth to earth, ashes to ashes,
dust to dust.
Amen.
[mourners chattering]
[Renai] It was a beautiful service
for a beautiful grandma.
She loved you guys so much.
Your mother was a fine friend, Josh.
Thank you.
I miss Grandma.
I know she misses you too, Kali.
Dead people don't miss anything.
Okay, that's not true,
and she does miss you.
See you guys next weekend, okay?
Dalton.
Dalton!
-See what I mean?
-He's just anxious about leaving.
For school next week.
I know. Yeah, no.
Um...
Thank you for organising all this.
I just haven't had the bandwidth.
Why don't you drive him to school?
You have a few weeks
until all your students show up.
-Nah, he wouldn't want me to.
-He's not the parent, you are.
If you don't want to,
then that's a different story, but--
No, I can't.
Why?
Wh--
[scoffs] It was just an idea.
Maybe some way
that you guys could connect, that's all.
He's gonna be gone soon, so...
Anyway, think about it.
Bye. See you, man.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Hey.
Do I know you?
I knew your mother.
Years ago. Um...
But we lost touch.
What's your name?
Carl.
[unsettling music playing]
Nice to meet you, Carl.
Appreciate you coming.
I'm sorry I grabbed you.
-I got a lot on my mind.
-I'm sure.
Death floods the mind with memory.
But there's always new ones
to make, right?
Yeah.
Bye, Josh.
-[whispers] Carl.
-[car engine starts]
[sighs]
Carl.
[typing clacking]
Uh...
[exhales]
[Josh] What did you just tell me?
Well, just tell me, Dalton.
Or change it?
Do you wanna clean--?
Do you wanna keep the same diaper on?
Yeah?
I tell you what.
We can just clean out the diaper
and then put the same diaper back on.
Would you like that?
You like that? Okay, I'll do that, then.
What kind of outfit do you want?
Oh... oop.
-Oop. What kind of outfit do you want?
-[baby Dalton babbling]
Yeah? Well, tell me.
All you got to do is talk to me.
[Renai laughing on recording]
Come on.
It's the greatest guy in the world.
Oh, shit.
Uh...
I mean...
Yeah, great.
All right.
[ominous tone plays]
Okay.
[car engine starts]
[haunting music playing]
["Roll With the Changes"
playing over radio]
♪ As soon as you are able
Woman I am willing ♪
♪ To make the break
That we are on the brink of ♪
♪ My cup is on the table ♪
You hungry?
♪ Our love is spilling
Waiting here for you... ♪
You're gonna have
to pull out of your little funk
or it's gonna be a long few days.
♪ But if you're tired
Of the same old story ♪
♪ Oh, turn some pages ♪
♪ I'll be here when you are ready... ♪
Mom said you got that art teacher
you wanted. What's his name?
Her name. Armagan.
She good?
She's the best.
Good job.
I mean, she better be,
with what we're paying.
["Calling My Children Home" playing]
♪ Those lives were mine
To love and cherish ♪
♪ To guard and guide along life's way ♪
[Josh] All right.
Let the fun begin.
♪ Oh God forbid... ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you.
Yeah, you. Come here.
Hey, man, welcome to JPU.
♪ Alas should go astray... ♪
Kappa Tau, huh? I was, uh, Kappa Z.
Long time ago, of course.
I'll take one for him.
Just put it... Thank you.
Hey!
♪ They live so far away ♪
♪ Oh may they hear my calling... ♪
Sorry.
Oh, all right.
You get first dibs.
Why don't you pick a bed?
Mom got you this, uh, power station thing.
What do you got here?
You got, uh, two outlets...
USB port, and, uh, two jumper cables,
which are useless.
There we go. Okay.
Okay.
Still need this?
Guess Mom put it in there.
Wow.
This is intense.
This what you been working on?
-Put it back.
-No, it's really good.
Did you do this from memory?
It's from a photo I found at the house.
Wow, looks like she's, uh...
Like she's hiding something?
That's what it feels like.
Felt like. The last few years.
She had a tough go, you know,
being a single mom.
Yeah, yeah, that's... Yeah, that's tough.
Guess I didn't make the wall, huh?
I don't blame you.
You know, I'm sorry
I haven't been around lately.
Of course,
my dad wasn't around at all, but...
So it could be a lot worse.
I've just been a little foggy
past few years.
I don't know, my brain just...
I just...
haven't been able to manage a time
for, uh, you and your brother and sister.
Have you ever thought about getting help?
I'm just trying to push through.
[grunts]
-Are you Dalton Lambert?
-Yeah. Are you...?
Chris Winslow.
-Everything cool, fellas?
-Yeah, no, everything's fine.
I just-- I thought
my roommate would be a, um...
Um...
Uh, a guy.
[Dalton] Yeah.
Oh.
I just figured it's a liberal arts school,
and we mean "liberal."
Yeah, probably just confused
by the name "Chris."
Right. 'Cause that would never happen
with a name like "Dalton."
You know, I'm gonna go down
to the housing office
and get this all sorted out.
No, no, no.
Please, father of Dalton. Allow me.
I clearly interrupted some boy bonding.
I'll be back.
[Josh chuckles]
Hey. Uh...
I snagged this for you.
You should check it out.
If you hate it, no worries.
But you're not gonna hate it.
You really don't know me, do you?
I mean, you really think
I wanna join a frat?
It's just a party, Dalton.
Go. Have fun.
I mean, do it for me. I drove you here.
-You didn't even want to.
-Of course I did.
Stop lying to me!
I heard what Mom said at the funeral.
Well, I still did it.
Oh, so that makes you
father of the year now?
At least you've got a father.
Stop blaming your dad
for shit you screwed up.
He left like 40 years ago. Get over it.
God knows I'm not gonna be defined by you.
Are you kidding me?
After all we have done for you?
When did you become
this ungrateful, little shit?
No wonder Mom divorced you.
Thanks for the ride.
[poignant music playing]
[students chattering]
[engine starts]
[showers running]
[students chattering]
[melodica playing pop upbeat pop melody]
You can tell it's Shania Twain, right?
Yeah.
So, what'd they say at housing?
[Chris] They said, "Tough titties."
I got to sleep here tonight.
But I'll get a new room tomorrow,
so it's not a permanent thing.
Heartbreak, right?
-You're in the art school, I take it?
-Yeah. Are you music?
Math. I thought about music,
but the artist's life
is one of nomadic instability
and much gnashing of teeth.
But I'm sure you'll be super successful.
[chuckles]
-You wanna blow my hooter?
-What?
Do you play?
Oh. [chuckles]
-Uh, just a little piano.
-It's the same thing. Just blow.
My cooties are good cooties.
[playing cheerful melody]
What's that?
It's just something my mom wrote.
Sweet.
So...
what's some weird shit about you?
I don't know.
Uh... "I don't know."
Come on, man. Everybody's weird.
You first.
On Sundays, I wear a monocle
and I order takeout with a British accent.
That is weird.
Thank you.
Okay, sometimes I eat instant oatmeal,
uh, with no, like,
water or milk or anything.
It's just kind of dry.
You're bad at this.
Let's try again.
When I was 10, my parents died,
and I went to go live
with my Grandma Perkee,
who once went almost nearly blind
from a gnarly case of athlete's foot.
I don't remember when I was 10.
Like, the whole year.
What do you mean?
I was in a coma.
Viral meningitis.
At least that's what they told me,
the few times
that they would talk about it.
But I don't remember anything.
I don't even remember being sick.
It's like I woke up one day
and a whole year had passed.
That's awful.
And pretty weird.
Well done.
Yeah, honestly, I wish I could have
forgotten a whole year when I was a kid.
Could've used a little "meningi-gi."
Uh... you know,
there is one more weird thing about me.
Um, ever since my coma,
I've been afraid of the dark.
I was afraid of Barbie dolls
till I was, like... now.
[Dalton chuckles]
There's nothing wrong with being scared.
Just as long as you don't keep me up
with some bright-ass night light.
[Dalton] Um...
-Seriously?
-Sorry.
Oh, man. Whatever.
It's fine. I'll deal.
[poignant, pensive music playing]
[on recording] Hey, this is Dalton.
I can't get to the phone right now,
so leave me a message
and I'll give you a call back.
-[answering machine beeps]
-[Josh] Hey, bud. It's me.
Just making sure
you're getting settled in okay.
Um...
I was just, uh,
thinking about what you said...
and, um...
I don't know. I don't know
what's going on with me, but, um...
I'm gonna find out.
And I just wanted you to know that.
Okay, bye.
[students chattering]
[speaking indistinctly]
[Armagan] Hello.
I am Professor Armagan.
Shut off your phones.
Open your portfolios.
Pull out something that will interest me.
Pin it to your easel.
Stand beside your work.
Stand proud.
Alec Anderson.
Your technique is obvious.
-It looks like a photograph.
-Thanks.
That wasn't a compliment.
Tear it up.
Excuse me?
The drawing. Tear it up.
[Alec] I worked my ass off on this piece.
No one will miss it.
No way.
Alas, our first casualty.
Usually, I go through introductions
before someone quits.
-I didn't quit.
-Yes, you did.
You just haven't realised it yet.
You can go.
Good luck.
Any fool can learn technique.
Even master it.
It doesn't mean anything
if it doesn't come from inside.
I am not interested in the "rules of art."
We are going to break the rules.
Then I want you to break them again.
See how broken you can get.
[students gasp]
Dalton Lambert.
Yes, ma'am?
Why in the hell would you destroy
a beautiful drawing like that?
Once more for good measure?
Wasn't so hard, was it?
Good. You must let go of your past.
Shed your skin in order to grow.
I'll count backwards from ten.
With each number,
I want you to sink
further and further into yourself.
Do not lift the charcoal from the paper.
Ten...
nine...
eight, seven, six...
five...
four, three, two...
one.
[ominous music playing]
Draw whatever your soul brings forth.
An experience that defines you.
You've got to be willing to dredge up
your ugliest, innermost thoughts.
-[yells]
-[gasps]
[haunting music playing]
Is it keeping you in or out?
You'll have headphones on.
The machine is quite loud,
but you'll be able to hear me.
I'm going to need you to stay as still
as possible throughout the procedure.
If you feel like you need
to get out of there,
give the call ball a squeeze,
we'll give you a break.
You good?
Overjoyed.
All aboard.
-Hit this.
-[Josh exhales]
[MRI machine whirring]
[Brower over headphones]
Okay. You comfortable, Josh?
Yep. Let's just get this over with.
[MRI machine thumping]
[buzzes]
[MRI machine whirring and thumping]
Hello?
Dr Brower?
[Brower] There's someone with you.
What? What did you say?
Dr Brower, what did you say?
Wh-- [sighs]
[beeps]
Come on.
Um...
Okay, can you let me out, please?
-[call ball beeping]
-Hello, hey!
Can you let me out?
[Brower] The door is open.
Okay, okay. Let me out. Let me out.
Hey! Dr Brower.
Dr Brower, let me out.
Come on. Get me out of here.
Hello? Hey!
Just let me out.
Let me out, let me out, let me out.
Dr Brower. Come on.
[call ball beeping]
Let me out.
[panting]
[intense music playing]
[screaming]
[gasping]
Okay. Come on.
Mr Lambert?
-What was that? What was that?
-Are you okay?
-Who was that? Why did the lights go out?
-Calm down.
You said the lights went out?
All the lights went out
and I got stuck in there, man.
And I saw...
-What...
-Mr Lambert,
you've been asleep for 15 minutes.
You went right out.
Your MRI went perfectly.
-What?
-Take your time to get dressed.
Come on through.
[keyboard clacking]
[Brower]
There's nothing physically wrong with you.
No growths or spots on the brain.
Nothing to be concerned about.
That's good news, Mr Lambert.
Yeah, no, I know, I, uh...
I guess I was just hoping
for something real.
Something that could explain this fog.
The memory issues you're talking about,
they could be spurred on
by a number of things.
Increased stress, change in daily habits.
Have there been any disruptions
in your home life?
My, uh, mom passed away recently.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Not to mention my son left for school,
and, uh, my ex-wife
hardly talks to me, so...
-That certainly sounds stressful.
-Yeah.
Maybe a grief counsellor be of some help?
Yeah. Sure. Probably would.
Do you have any history
of mental illness in your family?
Mental illness?
It's nothing to be alarmed about.
It can be informative
as we try to make a diagnosis.
Not that I'm aware of.
It's worth looking into.
Meanwhile, there are exercises,
games you can do
to stimulate your memory.
Matching games. Like kids do.
You want me to play kids' games?
We can learn a lot from kids.
Yeah.
[students chattering]
[Dalton] Thanks.
[haunting music playing]
[gasps]
[ominous music playing]
[screams]
[gasping]
Whatcha doin'?
Got my new room assignment today.
So, alas, no more panty parties.
But consolation, I'm in 323 now.
Right above you.
So be cautious, young man,
lest I hear you slap your sausage
in the dead of night.
-You want to join a frat?
-What?
Oh.
No, it's just something my dad got me.
We should go.
We can make fun of their khaki pants
and trust funds.
Unless you're not done redecorating.
Come on, Dolphin.
Do something nice for your old man.
What's the worst that could happen?
["Arab Money" blaring over speakers]
May I offer you some diaper pudding?
Uh, I'm good.
Oh, no.
Whatever.
Seriously?
Oh, come on.
Quit your bitching and come here.
To memorialize the night
that Dalton Lambert actually has fun!
[students yelling and laughing]
[students] Go! Go! Go!
[students yelling and chattering]
What's "frat juice"?
-Don't ask.
-[Nick] Hey, hey, hey!
-Everyone, my name's Nick.
-[music stops]
[frat members] Nick the Dick!
Nick the Dick! Nick the Dick!
Welcome to the Kappa House,
and welcome back to school, baby.
[students whoop]
I'm just here
to remind you fine folks that frats,
they're under attack.
Right, and we must protect
our right to party
and to be awesome.
White, Black, brown, or blue,
you're all welcome at JPU,
provided that you recognise
and respect
that the frat house is the last house
where men can still be men.
[student coughs]
Whoo!
Thank you.
Now, we got a lot of drinking
to do tonight,
but pace yourselves.
We do not need another incident.
-[students chattering]
-This party's lame.
Confirmed. So let's go upstairs
and look through everyone's shit.
["How U Feel?" playing over speakers]
♪ But you came right on time
Can we turn off all these lights? ♪
♪ Can I roll up, get a lil' high?
Every time I look in your eyes ♪
♪ I look away mesmerised ♪
♪ And you shine brighter than the stars
That decorate the night sky... ♪
[Chris] Yeah.
[students chattering and cheering]
[Dalton] We should make this quick.
Permission to proceed granted.
Wait.
Huh. Oh. Wow.
Oh, no.
This is Nick's room.
And this is Nick's butthole cream.
I'm going to go spread this
on the communal crapper. BRB.
Wait.
[man retching]
[Dalton] Hey, man...
[retching continues]
Hey, man, you okay?
You need water or something?
[man] Make it stop.
-Make it stop.
-[haunting music playing]
Make it stop.
Close the door.
Close the...
Close the door!
[Nick] I'll be right back.
I just need some supplies.
Hey, Paige. I am Nick.
♪ Tonight is your night, bro
Tonight is the night ♪
Got you.
Come on, man.
Just be you, bro.
You want to dance?
A dance would be nice.
We can dance.
Let's dance.
♪ Tonight is the night, bro ♪
[gasping]
[Dalton screams]
[Chris] Be quiet!
Are you good?
I think I just saw something...
What?
We need to go.
-Now.
-But this is just getting fun.
-[Nick] Is somebody in my room?
-Shit, shit, shit.
One of you peckerwoods is about
to get the hammer drop.
-What the hell?
-[gasps]
Oh, my God. So sorry.
We were just looking for some privacy,
you know?
We were gonna do it.
I'd rather watch my parents do it.
But you should stick around.
We might get drunk enough
to find you attractive.
[frat bros laugh]
Even though you look like a clown.
Nick the Dick, huh?
I'm more partial to kick the dick.
-[yelps]
-[frat bro] Oh!
[Chris] Run!
That was pretty quick thinking
back there, right?
I, uh...
Oh, crap.
[groans] I should've asked
before I kissed you, right?
I am sorry. I was just...
I was going on instinct.
-Oh, no...
-Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's just, I, um...
I'm just sorry for what he said to you.
Oh.
Whatever.
You think I care
what Vineyard Vines thinks?
He should be so lucky.
[Josh on recording]
Hey, buddy, it is, uh, me again.
Um, I went to the doctor.
Um, and everything's okay.
Well, not okay.
But I'm getting to the bottom of it.
So, uh, just give me a call when you can.
All right, I, uh...
I'm really sorry, Dalton,
about what I said the other day.
All right, bye.
[haunting music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[floorboards groaning]
-[plays discordant tones]
-Where's my mayonnaise?
Who is it?
[playing cheerful melody]
[Chris gasps]
[ominous music playing]
[gasping]
[thudding]
[suspenseful music playing]
[knocking on door]
Please don't tell me
you're really just a creep.
What? No.
Then what the hell is going on?
Come on in.
Something's happening to me.
I'm seeing things, crazy things.
You know that kid at the frat house
that they talked about, with the incident?
-Uh-huh.
-I saw him. And he was dead.
It started with an art exercise,
and she asked us to dig deep
into a memory, into our subconscious.
So I did and I drew this door.
You really need to lay off the frat juice.
I'm serious.
Tonight, I was painting and I fell asleep.
And when I woke up, this lantern appeared.
It was like a dream,
but it wasn't a dream.
And then I walked to your room.
I know how this sounds.
I feel like
I'm getting closer to something.
Or something's getting closer to me.
[haunting music playing]
You got an extra pillow?
-[dog barking]
-[sighs]
[birds singing outside]
[ominous music playing]
Okay.
Foster.
Renai.
Dalton.
Kali.
Dalton?
Dalton.
Mom.
[sighs]
Okay.
Okay, Mom, help me out.
[unsettling music plays]
Kali.
Dalton. Dalton.
Mom.
Mom?
[sighs] I don't know. I don't know.
Okay.
-[intense music playing]
-[Josh yells]
[panting]
Damn it.
[ominous tone plays]
[intense music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
[gasping]
[Armagan] Chiaroscuro.
The dance of light and shadow.
An effect used not only
to create volume and definition,
but also a specific, unseen light source.
Right. This is one of Goya's best.
The negative space draws our eyes
towards Saturn.
-Does it represent darkness or some void?
-[haunting music playing]
Goya mastered it on the canvas,
but family problems and health issues
sent this once-revered court painter
into a dark spiral,
leading him to create this grisly portrait
of a father devouring his son.
This balance between light and dark
is what we're after.
Get ready.
Your own experiences shape your artwork.
Embrace them. Use them.
Sink deep into the darkness of memory.
Ten...
nine...
eight...
seven...
six...
five...
four...
three...
two...
one...
-[yelling]
-[gasps]
[Josh sighs]
[unsettling, pensive music playing]
-[Foster] 'Sup, nerd?
-A red door.
Uh, a purple pecker.
Come on, man. Doesn't that
mean anything to you? A red door?
You sound weirder than usual.
It's a thing from art class.
It's a painting.
We had to find a memory.
I thought it was something
from our childhood.
Did you ask Mom?
No, I don't want to worry her.
Why would that worry her?
-I don't know.
-This what happens when you go to college?
You get all cryptic and shit?
I guess.
Well, I'm not going, then.
[call disconnects]
[groans]
[haunting music playing]
So after the whole spooky
dream-not-a-dream thing the other night,
I started thinking:
"Yeah, okay, Dalton's a weirdo,
but he's not insane, right?"
I'm gonna need that key back.
Right. So I started poking
around the old interwebs...
and guess what?
You're not crazy at all.
You are an astral projector.
Check this out.
Looks like they filmed it
in between shifts at Best Buy.
Hey, guys, this is Spectral Sightings.
I'm Specs, this is Tucker. Say hi, Tucker.
-No.
-Okay. We are PPI,
Professional Paranormal Investigators.
Today, we're gonna be talking about
something that dozens of you
have been asking us about.
-Astral projection.
[Specs] It's a real phenomenon.
Our physical body falls asleep
and our astral body leaves
that physical body...
and floats off into another realm.
-That's exactly what it feels like.
-See, I told you. It's cool, right?
Our former mentor, Dr Elise Rainier,
she had a name for this other realm.
-She called it The Further.
-Hold on.
[Elise on video] I am Elise.
It's nice to see you all.
So I'm here to talk to you
about astral projection...
and The Further.
Okay...
give me a minute here.
Three...
two...
one.
The Further...
is a dark realm...
filled with tortured souls of the dead...
and some are doomed...
to live the worst mistakes of their lives
over and over and over for all eternity.
When you astral project...
or you travel to this realm...
these are the souls...
that you awaken with your presence.
They can smell you.
The presence of life.
Life is what they crave,
more than anything.
So the further you travel...
[unsettling music playing]
the riskier the journey becomes.
They want life, and they can come
to our world to get it.
Keep a steady stride.
[mouse clicks]
[groans] I see those gears turning.
What is it?
-That kid from the frat house?
-The pukey kid?
Yeah. He said something to me.
He said, "Close the door."
I'm sure he did.
It probably wasn't his proudest moment.
Yeah, but what if
he meant something else?
What if he was talking about this door?
So, what? You want to go back and ask him?
Seriously?
I need to know.
Look, I feel bad for the dude, I do,
but dark realms are typically
places I try to avoid.
There's something important
about this painting, Chris.
I have to find out.
Okay.
It's not like Nick the Dick is just gonna
let you waltz into his bedroom
and chat with the ghost in his toilet.
He'll never know I'm there.
[students laughing and chattering]
So, what's the plan?
-I got this.
-[woman] Can I help you?
[in British accent] Hello.
I have left my brassiere
in Nicholas's room,
and I was wondering
if he is perchance home?
I think he's upstairs studying with Paige.
[Chris in normal voice]
Great job, Dolphin.
I'm gonna read you this.
It's called In Flames.
Very vulnerable piece.
"Looking across a campfire..."
I need a room with darkness.
Okay.
Then what?
You gonna float through the air
and do a little "Ooh"?
I'm not like a ghost.
And you never will be
with that attitude, Casper.
Bingo.
What are the chances
those bedsheets are crusty?
Probably snap like a taco shell.
I'll take the dirty floor.
[Chris] Okay...
-Can you give me a little space, please?
-Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Okay, you ready?
-[ominous music playing]
-Ten, nine...
eight, seven...
six, five...
four, three...
two, one.
Are you floating yet?
[door opens]
[hinges groan]
Farewell, traveller.
[unsettling, pensive music playing]
[whispers] You out here, Dalton?
[Nick] ...creative writing double major.
But I'm also crazy good at finance,
so I don't want to waste that gift.
How long do you have to keep that on?
Oh.
Yeah, it's good now.
My pores are good.
[Nick] Oh.
-[stomach gurgles]
-[groans]
I'm gonna be a while.
Gross.
Dalton?
Dalton.
Someone turn on the lights!
[Chris] Dalton.
Dalton.
Dalton, wake up.
-[Nick] Guys! Seriously.
-Chris.
[Nick] Guys, who's messing with me?
[sick kid] Close the door!
-Close the door!
-[yells]
Dalton?
-[intense music playing]
-[choking]
-[sick kid] Close the door!
-Chris!
Oh, God.
[snarls]
Come on!
[gasping]
[Dalton] Chris.
What...?
[ominous music playing]
[microfilm viewer clinking and clanking]
Come on.
What?
[Dalton] Chris.
-Chris. Hey. I didn't mean it like that...
-Don't.
I just wanted to see if you're okay.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry. I didn't know
anyone could get hurt in the real world.
Well, they can.
You have no idea what you're messing with.
I can't be a part of this, Dalton.
And neither should you.
Because next time, you might not wake up.
[ominous music playing]
[knocking on door]
-Hey.
-Hi.
Uh, it's not your weekend.
Kali's at a sleepover and Foster's...
I'm not here for the kids.
Can we talk?
Sure.
[line dialling]
[Foster] Wow, two calls in one week.
-[Dalton] Come on, man.
-Haven't you made any friends yet?
Tell me everything you remember
about my coma.
You should talk to Mom.
I think these...
-things I'm drawing, they...
-The door?
And now a guy with a hammer.
-A hammer?
-I think they could be clues from my past,
thoughts that have disappeared
'cause of my coma.
-I don't know why they're coming out now--
-Wait. Dalton.
What is it?
I've had this image in my mind for years.
Mom always says it's not real.
It's just a bad dream. But...
Tell me, little brother. Come on.
Okay. We're in a room somewhere.
Like a basement.
You remember that?
[crying]
Dalton, you there?
[tense, unsettling music playing]
All I ever wanted
was to be better than my father.
You know that. Just to be a good dad.
You were. You are, Josh.
Well, Dalton would disagree.
Well, if it's any consolation,
I can't even get him to call me back.
My dad abandoned his family, and...
I've done the same thing.
No, you haven't.
You're not him, Josh,
and you're allowed to be angry at him.
I am angry.
I've been angry for a long time.
Angry at a man that I have never met.
Angry at a man that jumped off the roof
of a mental hospital in 1978.
For more than 40 years,
that man has been dead and gone.
My dad.
Ben Burton.
So how in the hell is he terrorizing me
here, now, in the real world?
-He attacked me at Mom's place...
-He attacked you?
Yeah. So am I just crazy, or...?
I don't know. He, uh...
left this for my mom the day he died.
What ends with him?
-Josh...
-Is that the answer? Am I just crazy?
Is his madness inside of me?
Is that why I've been so lost
the past few years?
Did I pass this curse on to our kids?
Is he gonna haunt them...
-Josh, Josh.
-...like he haunted me?
Why didn't my mother say
anything about this?
Stop.
You're not crazy.
Then what's happening to me?
[ominous, pensive music playing]
[cell phone buzzing]
Dalton.
So Dalton and I could travel
to some other...
dimension...
where we were haunted
by ghosts and goblins.
[Renai] More like entities,
like the one in those photos
that haunted you.
And your father, he saw them too, and...
Maybe he's just reaching out.
Back then, he told your mom.
She didn't understand.
-She didn't know how to help him.
-Help him like you helped us?
By suppressing our memories?
We all thought it was for the best, Josh.
You included.
But you got foggy.
The suppression, it slowed you down.
And your mom and I,
we didn't know what to do.
And I was too scared
to tell you the truth.
[haunting music playing]
Dalton was right.
He said my mom had secrets,
that she was hiding something from us.
I just never thought you did too.
-For ten years...
-You have no idea...
-...you have kept this away from me.
-...how hard it has been for me.
-Just why? Why? Why?
-You don't understand--
Because you tried to kill our family.
You chased us around the house
with a goddamn baseball bat!
-What?
-I mean, I knew
that it wasn't you. I knew it was that...
thing in those photos, but the kids?
They don't understand.
All those night terrors that Foster had.
I've been lying to our children
for a decade,
telling them those memories aren't real.
"They're just your imagination.
Dad's not gonna hurt you."
-I couldn't.
-But you did.
Doesn't matter to them
what was controlling you.
What they saw was your face.
It was you who was causing all that pain.
That's why I pulled away. I just...
I couldn't live like that anymore.
You know...
we could've gotten through this together.
Is this you?
Dalton just sent this to me.
He's been having nightmares and visions.
Something about a red door.
And now this.
What do we do?
[haunting music playing]
[thudding footsteps overhead]
[door closes]
[Josh yelling and children crying]
[young Foster] I'm scared.
[Renai] It's gonna be okay.
-It's gonna be okay.
-[young Foster] I don't know...
It's okay. Nothing's gonna happen to us.
I promise you, okay?
Take care of your brother, Dalton.
-Okay.
-[Foster crying]
[young Dalton] Here.
[young Foster] But why is Daddy mad at us?
[Josh yelling]
[thudding]
-[thuds]
-[crying]
[young Dalton] Mommy. Mommy...
I can go into the dark place
and find Daddy.
-[Renai] No, it's too dangerous.
-I can do it, though.
Okay, just be careful.
Come on.
[intense music playing]
[Josh yelling]
[Renai screams]
No! Stop! What are you doing?
Stop! What are you doing?
Dad, please, just stop.
Just stop!
No!
Stop!
[screaming]
[gasps]
[Tiny Tim] And now, my dear friends,
I'd like to dedicate this song
to all of you out there.
Wherever you may be,
this song is for you.
["Fill Your Heart" playing on gramophone]
[gasps]
♪ Fill your heart with love today ♪
♪ Don't play the game of time ♪
♪ Things that happened in the past ♪
♪ Happened in your mind ♪
♪ In your mind, only in your mind ♪
♪ In your mind ♪
♪ Forget your mind and you'll be free ♪
[snarls]
[gasps]
[knocking on door]
-[knocking continues]
-[Chris] Just checking on you.
Okay.
Sitting on the floor, being weird.
That's normal.
So you're good, right? Because...
I thought that when the power went out,
that maybe you were messing
with that dark realm shit again.
[chuckles] And I know
that you don't really care for the dark.
So I figured...
I would illuminate your room,
much like how I illuminate your life.
I'm not afraid of the dark anymore.
Okay.
Well, I hauled these
all the way down here,
so they're going up anyway.
Even though you're totally
freaking annoying.
So, um, listen...
I got your text
and I wrote a snarky response.
And then I deleted it,
because Grandma Perkee always told me
to never escalate an argument over text.
Doesn't convey tone.
But, I mean, if you want my opinion...
here it is.
Don't go digging around in your past.
Some things are just better
left buried, you know?
And...
sometimes you just have to move on.
[suspenseful music playing]
Dalton?
Hey.
[Dalton breathing raggedly]
Dalton. You okay?
-[intense music playing]
-[yells]
["Tip Toe Thru the Tulips"
playing distortedly on gramophone]
♪ Knee-deep in flowers, we'll stray ♪
♪ We'll keep the showers away ♪
♪ And if I kiss you in the garden ♪
♪ In the moonlight ♪
♪ Will you pardon me? ♪
♪ And tiptoe through the tulips with me? ♪
-[ominous music playing]
-[haunting indistinct whispers]
[Josh] Dalton.
[Chris] Dalton.
Dalton?
[clock ticking]
[Josh gasping]
[ominous music playing]
Dalton?
[music intensifies]
[snarls]
No.
Oh, no! No, no, no!
[Josh] Daddy's here.
I'm gonna get you
out of this place, Dalton.
We're gonna get out of here
and we're gonna get home, okay?
We're never going back there.
[Chris] Dalton. What?
[breathing raggedly]
Dalton.
Dalton, tell me you're in there.
Dalton, I know you're in there.
But if you touch me again,
I'm gonna fuck you up.
[chains clanking]
[screaming]
Dad, no!
You tried to kill me.
-It wasn't me.
-I saw you!
Dalton, these things,
they can possess our bodies.
It happened to me,
and now he's done it to you.
[haunting music playing]
He's coming back for you.
We've got to go.
Come on.
[Dalton groaning]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[intense music playing]
-[screams]
[Josh] He's coming!
Go!
[roars]
Dalton, help me!
Help me hold the door!
[Dalton gasping]
[demonic hissing and groaning]
-[yells] No!
-We can't hold it back, Dad.
Son, we got to try.
Go, get away!
No!
No! No!
[Josh] Dalton, come on!
We got to find something to block it.
Something to seal it.
[Dalton] Come on, let's go.
-Dad, please.
-[young Dalton] Dad!
We have to go!
[ominous music playing]
It's okay.
You go.
Go.
Get away!
[Chris screams]
Get off!
[gasps]
[Dalton] No!
[heart thumping]
No! Oh, God.
Josh.
This ends with me.
[thumping slows]
[heart stops]
Paint?
[haunting music playing]
[heart thumping]
Paint. Dalton.
[yelling and grunting]
[intense music playing]
-[gasping]
-[snarls]
[roars]
[ethereal music playing]
[Chris] You need to get rid of that thing.
Burn it, forget about it.
No, no, forgetting it doesn't work.
We need to remember.
Even the things that hurt.
Dad?
[poignant music playing]
[gasps]
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Is Dalton okay?
-He's okay.
-Okay.
[cell phone ringing]
[Renai] That's him.
Dalton.
Is Dad back?
Yes. Yes, he's back. He's okay.
[dramatic music playing]
[inaudible dialogue]
See you next Friday.
Tell Foster to pack his history homework.
I'll help him with it.
Could come a little earlier if you want.
Join us for dinner.
Yeah, I'd like that. Thanks.
[hopeful music playing]
[Elise] Lovely home.
Oh, thanks.
-Do you live here?
-I hope so.
That's a weird answer.
Guess I'm just lost in memories.
They can flood the mind.
I know you.
May have seen me around.
I know your mother.
There's so much I want to tell her.
I know. And you can.
And you will. Someday.
You have a bright future ahead.
You and Dalton.
Keep a steady stride, Josh.
[music turns dramatic]
[engine starts]
[Josh] Wow.
I made the wall.
Yeah.
[Josh] I love you, son.
[Dalton] I love you too.
["Stay" playing]
♪ If this world is wearing thin ♪
♪ And you're thinking of escape ♪
♪ I'll go anywhere with you ♪
♪ Just wrap me up in chains ♪
♪ But if you try to go alone ♪
♪ Don't think I'll understand ♪
♪ Stay ♪
♪ Stay with me ♪
♪ In the silence of your room ♪
♪ In the darkness of your dreams ♪
♪ You must only think of me ♪
♪ There can be no in between ♪
♪ When your pride is on the floor ♪
♪ I'll make you beg for more ♪
♪ Stay ♪
♪ Stay with me ♪
♪ You better hope and pray ♪
♪ That you'll make it safe
Back to your own world ♪
♪ You better hope and pray ♪
♪ That you'll wake one day
In your own world ♪
♪ 'Cause when you sleep at night ♪
♪ They don't hear your cries
In your own world ♪
♪ Only time will tell ♪
♪ If you can break the spell
Back in your own world ♪
♪ Stay ♪
♪ Stay with me ♪
[song fades]
[haunting music playing]