(Mashle: Magic and Muscle)
In the battle with the Magia Lupus,
Lance easily defeated
the Third Fang, Wirth Madl.
Meanwhile, Mashle also defeated
the Second Fang, Abyss Razor.
Now, for Dot and Finn, the battle
with rivals is about to begin.
Let's go underground.
Disclose.
What a bossy old man.
-LOVE, I'll leave it to you here.
-Understood.
-Bastard, where are you going…
-Listen to me.
I'm the Fifth Fang of Magia Lupus.
You can call me little LOVE.
Hmm?
Do you like me?
Eh?
Speak up, do you like or dislike me?
Eh, this is the first time
we see each other?
Right, Finn?
Mm…mm.
So, am I cute?
Come on, speak up.
Am I cute or not?
Just say I'm cute.
How can she be so dramatic?
Anyone else seeing this would
probably get sick to death.
Am I cute or not?
But I like girls like her!
However,
I already have Lemon as my fiancee.
I'm very sorry.
I can't marry you.
What are these two talking about?
Have you liked someone?
Yes.
Do you like her more than you like me?
Sorry.
I see.
Then I'll
kill you.
How can she be so fickle?
Tornegus!
Explomb!
Oh, no.
There's obviously a gap in magical power
between me and two-mark Mages.
Girls
are born as princesses!
They should be praised,
spoiled and cherished.
Men who can't do these things
should just die!
Isn't that too extreme?
It's scary.
I'll ask you again.
Do you like or dislike me?
I can't stand it.
She has just met us.
And now she wants to kill everyone
who dislikes her. Is she crazy?
Speak up, am I cute?
But I like girls like her!
However,
I already have Lemon as my fiancee.
I apologize again.
I can't marry you.
I'm having a sense of déjà vu.
I'm really sorry.
I'm actually very faithful…
Ah!
Dot!
Nice.
What's nice about this?
I don't have a choice.
Men who don't cherish me should be killed.
That's what my dad told me.
Then please send a message to your dad.
He's wrong!
Explomb!
With your magical power,
you can't compete with me.
Don't you understand?
Tornegus!
What? He aimed in front of me
to block my vision.
He wants the magic wand.
What a pity.
You're too weak to defeat me.
Let me tell you some good news.
The Fourth Fang of Magia Lupus,
Milo Genius,
has the magic that can
petrify a specific person.
The premise to become a specific target
is to open the door leading underground.
It takes about two hours
to accumulate magic power
and use the spell.
That is to say,
if you can't defeat me within 30 minutes
and fight the Fourth Fang,
that mushroom head will turn into a stone.
But you can't possibly defeat me anyway.
Tornegus Cage!
Once you're caught in it,
you'll never get out!
Dot!
The mushroom head has made friends
with someone so weak.
I feel sorry for him.
But why does he have
to go against Lord Abel?
Challenging others without
knowing their strength.
He's as stupid as you.
It's hilarious.
My whole body hurts.
I can feel it deep in my bones.
Even breathing is difficult.
She is right.
The gap between our
strengths is too great.
There's no point in continuing the fight.
Hey, Dot.
You bought a new broom, right?
Swap it with mine.
Uh, well.
This broom is…
It's alright, right?
Mm…mm.
Thanks.
Here you go.
Thank you, sister.
Don't be a coward.
At least fight back.
It's okay.
Fighting back will only make it worse.
You give up so easily.
But
the thing is
when you make a real friend…
A real friend?
Right, someone who will
cry and get angry for you.
You might not meet one
in your entire life,
but if you do make such a friend,
you shall never betray them.
In other words, he's got
a lot of confidence.
Do you really think
you're the protagonist?
Right.
You're disgusting.
I really dislike
hot-blooded men like you.
I'm really a coward.
That's enough.
I got scared while my friend was mocked.
Come at me, scum.
My friend got so angry
for me!
So, in the meantime,
I'll finish off this freckled guy here.
Bye.
Tor…
…negus.
It can't end like this.
She mocked my friend!
What's with this amount of magic power?
He broke my spell?
Dot?
Can't you just pass out? So annoying!
Tornegus!
Explomb!
What?
They have been offset?
His magic power
has increased significantly?
Can he do that?
No, that mark…
I've heard of it.
He was born with a Warding
Cross mark on the forehead.
A battle demon race that
can release magic power
when their emotions reach a certain level.
The Ira Kreuz!
Mocking my friend is a great sin.
Machine gun
Explomb!
You said he will be
petrified in 30 minutes?
I won't let you stop him.
Come at me,
scum.
Die a hundred times!
What? He missed on purpose.
I have no interest in torturing women.
Get lost.
Before I change my mind.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Piece of cake!
Now he's back to his old self.
But he can handle the
Fifth Fang just by himself.
Has Dot also reached the two-mark level?
That's amazing, Dot…
Dot.
Sorry, Dot!
I thought you'd be able to finish off
the two one-mark Mages with ease.
How did you end up like this?
Ah?
Sorry about that.
The Fourth Fang.
He gave up the petrification
magic and showed himself?
They are not like people who
have ever proved to be
a real challenge.
Damn it.
He caught me off guard.
Can I beat the Fourth Fang
with my strength?
The Fourth Fang is the only first-year
student who made it into the Magia Lupus.
They're done for.
What was that?
A sword?
That magic is…
Damn it, what happened?
How did they
break my spell in an instant?
Why are you here?
Divine Visionary, Rayne Ames.
Wait, Rayne, why are you here?
The top one of Adler.
As a Divine Visionary,
he is also a student like us.
I don't need to panic.
Right, let's chat.
We all have our reasons, right?
Right?
What?
Don't waste my time.
Scum.
We're all students, right?
This is the magic of a Divine Visionary.
Why don't we transfer to Adler?
Oh no, he's so much stronger.
He is superior in every way.
Listen to me. I had no choice!
I'm also reflecting on
why I didn't disobey them.
Forgive me, please!
I see.
You're reflecting, huh?
The most important thing in this world
is actions, not words.
I would never believe
the words of scum like you.
People like you
have to learn your lesson the hard way.
I just need to beat you
until you dare not make
the same mistake again.
I heard he's also from Adler,
so he should be on our side, right?
What are you guys doing here?
Go back.
I still need to get the story out of him.
Okay.
Speak up.
So cruel.
By the way, why is the
Divine Visionary here?
-Senior.
-Huh?
Old man said that the followers of
the Innocent Zero have come here.
They must have suppressed their
magic power and sneaked in here.
Where are they hiding?
Getting nutrition, getting nutrition.
This isn't magic power.
But this immense pressure
is cause by him?
I need to hurry up.
Hurry up… huh?
I don't have much time.
Let me investigate you quickly.
Huh?
Now I'm going to use it to measure
your true magic power.
then I'll know if you're a student or not.
Huh?
Up to now, I have measured the magic
power of thousands of Mages. Spider.
Lord Rayne said,
if you're a regular Mage,
I'll let you go. Spider.
But…
Hey, what are you doing?
This is so dangerous.
Suspicious individual.
-Barbarian.
-Did he
use magic just now?
Ah, ba, ah ba ba ba ba.
It's zero.
No, it's impossible, impossible.
There might have been a mistake.
The measuring spider didn't react at all.
Could it be...
Eh?
Three Percent Partisan.
He turned my Partisan into a chair.
No way.
The measuring spider is so surprised
that it forgot to mention
"spider" at the end.
He really didn't use magic.
- I'm getting angry.
- He's not from Innocent Zero, but…
Let me try again.
Ten Percent
Partisan.
Lord Rayne wouldn't use it on a student.
This guy is dead…
What?
Swinging in the air?
Could it be...
Is that
a bunting stance?
Ah, he has used bunting moves to stop
all Rayne's attacks!
That is dangerous.
No, what's going on?
What's your name?
Mashle Burnedead.
Mashle.
We have an interesting
new student in our school.
Although his situation is quite special,
his mind is very strong.
I hope you can take
good care of him, Rayne.
His name is...
Burnedead.
So it's you.
Please forgive my rudeness earlier.
I'm very sorry.
I won't forgive you.
Here, take this as an apology.
A magic handkerchief that heals wounds.
Ah, alright.
Eh?
You like rabbits?
Thank you very much.
And be careful from now on.
You're going to see Abel, right?
How do you know?
I heard it from the old man that
you want to become a Divine Visionary too.
So you'll definitely run up against Abel.
Without a doubt, he is one of candidates
for Divine Visionary this year.
His puppet magic exceeds
what's required for a student.
Although I am surprised that you could
block my basic magic with bare hands,
it's a bit difficult for you to defeat
Abel since you cannot use the magic.
But I can use magic.
However,
Abel has almost all the credit coins.
By defeating him, you can
get all his credit coins
and become a strong candidate
for a Divine Visionary.
Nowadays, there are many problems
with the Realm of Magic.
So the stronger ones we have, the better.
Since you said you want to
become a Divine Visionary,
you must do it at all costs.
Alright.
I have other things to do.
Take care.
Ah, thank you for helping me so much.
I did all this for myself.
Don't get me wrong.
Goodbye.
He should be a good person.
He's an interesting kid who values
his friends' issues more than his own.
Well, maybe he's just simple-minded.
But it's a fact that your younger brother
was saved because of him.
To become a Divine Visionary
without knowing how to use the magic.
For that,
you have to prove to me
that you're better than Mages.
Is it here?
Should I push or pull this door?
Ah, push.
Do you have to break the door every time?
Actually,
I just knocked on it.
NEXT EPISODE
(Mashle Burnedead and the Survival of the Fittest)