<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="15287" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-12-25</startdate>
<enddate>2020-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Josee to Tora to Sakana-tachi</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Жозе, тигр і риба</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">ジョゼ虎</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">joseetora</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ジョゼと虎と魚たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Josee, the Tiger and the Fish.</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Josie, der Tiger und die Fische</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Josée, le tigre et les poissons</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Josée, la Tigre e i Pesci</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Josee, el Tigre y los Peces</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Её заветное желание</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">조제, 호랑이 그리고 물고기들</title>
<title xml:lang="es-CA" type="official">Josee, el Tigre i els Peixos</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Žose, tigras ir žuvis</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โจเสะ กับเสือและมวลหมู่ปลา</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="official">Josee: Khi nàng thơ yêu</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">喬瑟與虎與魚群</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">乔西的虎与鱼</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="531127">At the beginning I thought it was a regular story of a typical boy and a cute girl, however this movie has a beautiful message about important things in life and never give up chasing your dreams. 

Well directed, well animated, well executed and the music is superb too. Story is charming and pure, very emotional specially the ending, oh gosh, you must to watch it, I`m really surprised with the quality of this movie. 100% recommended!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://joseetora.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="59379" type="Original Work">Tanabe Seiko</name>
<name id="4894" type="Character Design">Iizuka Haruko</name>
<name id="4894" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iizuka Haruko</name>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="16596" type="Direction">Tamura Koutarou</name>
<name id="39819" type="Music">Evan Call</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr59379 [Tanabe Seiko]`s short romantic story.
http://anidb.net/ch113214 [Josee] is physically disabled and cannot walk without a wheelchair, so she has spent her life like a doll living in her own imagination world. http://anidb.net/ch113215 [Tsuneo] is a university student who has been chasing his dream. They meet by chance and are attracted to each other. Then, Josee decides to go with him to the outside world.
Source: Crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="690">8.49</permanent>
<temporary count="697">8.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>251288.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22907</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40787</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://joseetora.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Josee,_the_Tiger_and_the_Fish_(2020_film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ジョゼと虎と魚たち</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>370728</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>joseetora_movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>G3KHEVQ95</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B09PQ9JKNB</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="43">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tt12879624</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="44">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652837</identifier>
<identifier>movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="165" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>painting</name>
<description>Painting is the practice of applying paint, pigment, color or other medium[1] to a surface (support base). The medium is commonly applied to the base with a brush but other implements, such as knives, sponges, and airbrushes, can be used.
In art, the term painting describes both the act and the result of the action. Paintings may have for their support such surfaces as walls, paper, canvas, wood, glass, lacquer, clay, leaf, copper or concrete, and may incorporate multiple other materials including sand, clay, paper, gold leaf as well as objects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1298" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>drawing</name>
<description>The art or technique of representing an object or outlining a figure, plan, or sketch by means of lines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2677" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Osaka</name>
<description>Osaka Prefecture is a prefecture located in the Kansai region on Honshu, the main island of Japan. The capital is the city of Osaka. It is the center of Osaka-Kobe-Kyoto area.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214384.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3097" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-29">
<name>underwater</name>
<description>Underwater is a term describing the realm below the surface of water where the water exists in a natural feature such as an ocean, sea, lake, pond, or river.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4267" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-31">
<name>underwater diving</name>
<description>Underwater diving is the practice of descending below the water`s surface to interact with the environment. It is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6903 [acrobatic diving]. Please note that this tag is only about underwater diving as a sport; diving for e.g. salvaging shipwreck should be tagged with other, more specific tags.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4646" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-31">
<name>hospital</name>
<description>The place or building where sick people receive medical treatment in the hopes of curing their sickness. Also a dandy setting for creepy happenings in anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7885" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-11-07">
<name>Japanese production</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="113214" type="main character in" update="2021-09-15">
<rating votes="13">5.64</rating>
<name>Josee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43066" picture="172498.jpg">Kiyohara Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113215" type="main character in" update="2021-10-22">
<rating votes="5">7.51</rating>
<name>Suzukawa Tsuneo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="62240" picture="255526.jpg">Nakagawa Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113216" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-16">
<rating votes="6">7.83</rating>
<name>Ninomiya Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4432" picture="280839.jpg">Miyamoto Yume</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113217" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-16">
<rating votes="2">5.46</rating>
<name>Matsuura Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113218" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-09-15">
<rating votes="4">7.28</rating>
<name>Kishimoto Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="269818.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113219" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-09-15">
<rating votes="2">3.68</rating>
<name>Yamamura Chizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>265091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63014" picture="256915.jpg">Matsutera Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="119895" type="appears in" update="2021-09-29">
<name>Fujita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>265623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9288" picture="34149.jpg">Urayama Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="119896" type="appears in" update="2021-09-29">
<name>Mizushima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>265624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2258" picture="11054.jpeg">Uchida Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="119898" type="appears in" update="2021-09-29">
<rating votes="1">9.03</rating>
<name>Yukichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>265626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="266712.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="119900" type="appears in" update="2021-09-29">
<rating votes="1">9.03</rating>
<name>Kondou-kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>265628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34774" picture="129969.jpg">Obana Kanji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="231591" update="2020-12-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2020-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>GWDU8WG50</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="247668" update="2021-09-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2020-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="247669" update="2021-09-27">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2021-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タムラコータロー監督スペシャルインタビュー映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview with Director Tamura Koutarou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamura Koutarou Kantoku Special Interview Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="252782" update="2022-03-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer collection (01:33)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="252783" update="2022-03-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Original preview collection (01:33)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="252784" update="2022-03-11">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special pilot video (01:01)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="252785" update="2022-03-11">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Long PV (02:10)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="252786" update="2022-03-11">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Roadshow announcement CM collection (00:49)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
