This is the Magic Realm.
It is called the Magic Realm
because it is a world that has magic.
Flying through the sky with a broom,
levitating heavy objects,
creating something out of nothing...
Everyone can use magic at their will,
and in this world,
magic is a natural part of everyday life.
Magic is believed to be a gift
bestowed by God,
and mastery of magic determines
one's social status in this world.
In a corner of this world,
where dragons flying about is ordinary...
TREMBLE TREMBLE
Within that deep, deep forest,
there is one whose existence
defies the natural order.
Nothing like a cream puff
after pumping iron.
My name is Regro Burnedead.
I'm a chic and elegant 75-year-old
living with my son in a forest
far from other humans.
REGRO BURNEDEAD
I was quite reckless
in all sorts of ways in my youth,
but when you get as old as I,
very little bothers you.
And that’s because,
through my experiences,
I have acquired ways to combat stress.
How to combat stress...
RRRAAWR
Oh, Pops. I'm home.
MASH BURNEDEAD
Why!?
Why did you rip the door off
its hinges to come in, Mash!?
I couldn't remember
if I was supposed to push or pull.
How many years have you lived here!?
So I just kind of forced—
And you ended up breaking it!
Sorry, Pops. I'll fix it.
Oh, well... If you're repenting, then...
He's always so amenable
after each screwup.
RRRAAWR
Turn! Turn it! Turn it!
You need to turn it!
- Weird. It won't fit back in.
- That's the wrong position!
Huh? What'd you say?
Quit with the pounding, would you!?
Spit on the foundling?
No!
Sorry, Pops.
I'll fix it.
W-Well... Yeah, um...
Mash, did you finish
today's training routine?
Of course.
Hey, Pops.
I've been meaning to ask...
Why are all of my workouts physical?
Because you...
You're not like ordinary people.
You can't use magic at all
because you're different.
So the least I can do is...
Never mind. A story for another time.
Anyway, I'm heading out for a bit.
I'm trusting you to housesit.
- Okay.
- Don't break the door.
Don’t worry,
I learned how to fix it.
Learn how to open and close
the door instead!
Push in, or pull out...
Pull out! Pull out to open the door!
Anyways, I'm heading out.
I've told you countless times before,
but while I'm out, you must never
venture into the city.
Yeah, I won't.
Right. Mash, you’re such a good,
amenable son.
Now, I'll be on my way.
Be safe.
Sorry, Pops.
But I can't ignore
the call of an empty stomach.
Magic.
They're still just doing stuff
you can do with your hands.
Seven limited cream puffs, please.
Sure thing.
Oops. I got too excited
and couldn't hold back.
But these don't usually bend
just by squeezing your hand.
Sorry. Let me fix them.
Did you say, "fix"?
This should work.
Huh? Hold on...
Freaky? Huh? No, wait... Um...
Here. Thanks for waiting.
Thank you very much.
Hey, did you see it?
I don't see it anywhere on his face.
- No way.
- You're right. Nothing.
Unbelievable.
Sir, are you actually a...
No, never mind.
Thanks for your patronage.
This year's "Divine Visionary"
has been determined.
The one chosen as "Divine Visionary" is Rayne Ames,
a second-year at Easton Magic Academy,
a prestigious school in the Magic Realm.
This title is awarded
to the student demonstrating the highest degree
of excellence over the school year.
In addition to promotion to nobility,
Yeah, yeah.
Must feel good with all that talent.
recipients are gifted a grant
of one billion lond and are further awarded
provisional employment at the Bureau of Magic,
the highest legal organization.
Then you have me here,
living a dull life in a dull place.
He is expected to contribute greatly
for the prosperity of this country.
P-Please forgive me.
I only stole a little something.
Huh? Are you kidding me?
You gave me more work
with your petty crime.
I gotta make you regret it
so you’ll never trouble me again.
S-Stop it! Please!
What is it? I'm busy.
What? There's an unmarked brat
in the city?
Wonder what everyone
was all riled up about back there.
While I'm out, you must never
venture out into the city.
Sorry, Pops.
But it was worth coming here.
I got to eat Goblin Cream Puffs.
Yummy, yummy, yum...
Oh, sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What do you think you’re doing?
I'm workin' over here!
VODKA
ABV 90%
I'm a proud member of the magic police,
protecting ordinary folks like you!
And do I get any thanks? No!
The only thing I get is bottom-barrel pay!
Wanna have me
take out my stress on ya?
Would you like a cream puff?
I somehow feel sorry for you.
He's pitying me!
And it's half eaten!
Why would you give me
a half-eaten cream puff?
Ya aimin' for an indirect kiss or something?
Ya love me?
Are ya pickin' a fight?
That's basically pickin'
a fight with this country!
And whatcha gonna do
about my uniform? Huh?
What?
I'm sorry. I will wash
and return these clothes to you.
Now it ain't clothes!
Not as of this moment! Thanks to you!
What exactly did ya do, huh?
What's the matter, Terry?
Brad, this kid...
Don't make a riot over nothing.
More like, why the hell are you naked?
BRAD COLEMAN
Well, that's because this kid...
Must be him.
NOM NOM NOM NOM NOM
The unmarked brat from that report.
Wait.
NOM NOM NOM NOM NOM
Would anyone be eating cream puffs
in this kind of situation?
Hey, you over there.
Please excuse my son!
This will be a bit of a hassle,
but this may be my chance
for a promotion.
After them!
You idiot!
How may times have I told you?
Don't go to the city on your own!
I'm really sorry. I'll never go again.
He's really broken up about it.
It's clear he regrets his actions.
I can't stay mad at him.
Well, if that's the case, yeah.
But as punishment, you'll repeat
this morning's training routine.
Okay. And these cream puffs
are for you.
Oh, thank you.
Here.
Thanks, Pops.
He's such a good boy.
I thought a teenage son
would be really passionate,
rife with arguments
and rebellious streaks,
as you deepen your bonds
with each other.
But he's so amenable,
though a bit informal.
Well, I guess he's at an age
where he wants to get out.
We've lived here in hiding until now,
away from the city in this forest, for his sake.
But now the magic police
have caught wind of him.
I must act quickly.
What is that?
Hey, old geezer.
Where's the brat I saw earlier?
This is bad.
Five minutes is all I need
when I put my mind to it.
Time to head home and eat cream puffs.
"Crea" a puff, a creamy puff.
"Mp" a creamy, creamy puff.
"uff" a puff, a creamy puff.
Was I supposed to push or pull?
Guess it doesn't matter.
You knew and that's why
you hid that brat, right?
You know why magic has flourished
since the dawn of recorded history?
It's because we aggressively rid ourselves
of inferior blood unable to use magic.
It's a necessary sacrifice
for the world to go round.
Simply put, those who can't use magic
have no privileges.
Privilege to live, that is.
Or should I say,
they aren't supposed to live at all?
Spill it. Where’s the brat?
I-I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Sheltering the unmarked
is a serious offense, old man.
Hurry up and hand over the brat.
I refuse!
Fess up.
If you play nice and give us the brat,
I'll have my bosses spare you.
I won’t.
Never. I will never tell him.
Why can't you do something so simple!?
I'm sorry.
Your magic is weak.
You can't do anything properly!
Our bloodline has no need
for failures like you!
I'm sorry.
Hey! You can't even do something
as simple as this?
You're useless!
I-I apologize.
There are plenty of others
who can replace you!
I have always been a failure of a human.
I apologize.
- You failed again!
- I’m really sorry!
I kept failing
even after I became an adult.
You messed up again!
You're fired!
How can you keep living like that?
I'd already be dead
from embarrassment.
Completely unwanted.
I thought that's how my life would end.
If that's the case, then I should just...
This baby...
has no mark.
You were abandoned
because you were unmarked.
You're just like me.
In this moment, for the first time
in my life, I felt like someone needed me.
I swore on that day...
Even if we're not related by blood,
even if the entire world denied his existence,
I would always be a father to that boy!
Tell us where he is already, old man.
Run, Mash!
You old geezer!
You have to get away right now, Mash!
Hey! This means
he's still close by! Find him!
Yessir!
Run for it, Mash!
Damn you, old geezer!
- L-Let go of me!
- Run! Run!
Please let my words reach him.
Pipe it down, old geezer!
All that matters
is that you're safe! Please!
- Old man, hurry up and...
- Run away!
You are my one and only...
Run! Run away, Mash!
That's enough, old man.
I'll make you regret this.
Hey you! You had some nerve
earlier today when...
My second shirt today...
SLAP SLAP SLAP SLAP SLAP
Why...
Why didn't you run, Mash?
Because we're family.
You're all I've got.
Sorry for being selfish, Pops.
But since I'm here...
I might as well send you guys to hell.
What a joke.
You can't even use magic.
How are you going to take me down?
What an idiot. Brad used to be
on the Bureau of Magic's Security Force.
Regular mages around here
don't hold a candle to him.
And a magic-less chump
wants to take him on?
He won't stand a chance!
It'll be over in three seconds.
That’s the spell that drove away a dragon
in his Bureau of Magic's Security Force days!
I didn't think I would get to see it here!
Eat this.
Nalcom Pas!
Mash!
Huh? Did he...
My Nalcom Pas... He just...
He slapped it down? Like, “paff”?
Can magic be paff'ed just like that?
I drove a dragon away
with that spell, you know?
What? There's no way.
Not bad, brat!
But how about this?
That magical energy output!
Is he trying to destroy
this entire area?
Hold on, Brad!
You shouldn't do that!
Nalcom Pas Diagorus!
Damn it!
This brat...
He's killing the momentum
with his knees!
What a soft touch!
All right, then how about this?
And now he's juggling!
Look at those dribbling moves!
This brat is totally
making a fool of me.
Pops, I'm gonna borrow your wand.
What’s going on?
He can use magic after all?
Doesn't matter.
Ordinary magic
won't even reach me anyway...
I've never seen anyone
use a magic wand like that before.
Threaten my family again...
and I'll kill you.
TREMBLE TREMBLE
His training was only meant
to teach him self-defense.
How is this physically possible?
Either way, we're done for.
Even if we fend them off
for now, in due time...
Interesting.
Let's make a deal, Mushroom Head.
Do what I ask, and I'll let you
and the old geezer slide.
A deal?
Once a year in this country,
one exceptional student
is revered as one of God's chosen.
It's called the "Divine Visionary."
Enroll in a magic school
and be chosen as one.
Simply put, if you're selected,
it means God has accepted you.
Which means, society will accept you.
I just want the fortune and prestige
that comes with it.
I'll back you up, of course.
Don't listen to him, Mash!
Those are the words of someone
who was an enemy until moments ago!
It's up to you
if you want to be skeptical or not.
But if you refuse, we’ll hunt you down
for the rest of your life.
If I'm after you,
the whole country will be, too.
You'll be okay because you're tough.
But what about the old man?
A life where you can never feel at ease,
and unable to set foot in a city.
Well, the choice is yours.
Spend the rest of your life
being hunted down,
or brace yourself to die
and try turning the tables?
- You got a deal.
- Are you sane? It's a magic school!
I'll be fine, Pops. My motivation
is stronger than anyone else.
This isn't about motivation!
Besides...
I want us to be able
to live in peace again.
You're such a good boy.
My son!
MY SON
Living in peace with Pops.
If it's a world that won't allow
something as natural as that...
Then I've got no choice but to crush it.
With my fist.
NEXT EPISODE
MASH BURNEDEAD AND THE MYSTERIOUS MAZE